<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>The abstract of the claims of all persons claiming as innocents in the city, county of the city, and county of Dublin</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1663</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 112 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 35 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2013-12">2013-12 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A75049</idno>
            <idno type="STC">Wing A128</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC R231147</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">99897243</idno>
            <idno type="PROQUEST">99897243</idno>
            <idno type="VID">136892</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A75049)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 136892)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1641-1700 ; 2469:3)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>The abstract of the claims of all persons claiming as innocents in the city, county of the city, and county of Dublin</title>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>[4], 64 p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>printed by John Crook, printer to the Kings most excellent Majestie, and are to be sold by Samuel Dancer, bookseller in Castlestreet,</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>Dublin :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1663.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>Land settlement --  Law and legislation --  Ireland --  Early works to 1800.</term>
               <term>Allotment of land --  Ireland --  Early works to 1800.</term>
               <term>Ireland --  History --  1660-1688 --  Early works to 1800.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2012-05</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2012-06</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-01</date>
            <label>Colm MacCrossan</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-01</date>
            <label>Colm MacCrossan</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-02</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:136892:1" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <p>THE ABSTRACT Of the CLAIMS Of all Perſons Claiming as INNOCENTS In the City, County of the City, And County of DUBLIN.</p>
            <figure>
               <figDesc>blazon or coat of arms of the British royal family</figDesc>
               <head>
                  <q>DIEV ET MON DROIT</q>
               </head>
               <p>HONI SOIT QVI MAY Y PENSE</p>
               <p>C2 R</p>
            </figure>
            <p>
               <hi>Dublin,</hi> Printed by <hi>John Crook,</hi> Printer to the Kings moſt Excellent <hi>Majeſtie,</hi> and are to be ſold by <hi>Samuel Dancer,</hi> Bookſeller in <hi>Caſtleſtreet,</hi> 1663.</p>
         </div>
         <div type="proclamation">
            <pb facs="tcp:136892:2"/>
            <pb facs="tcp:136892:2"/>
            <head>By His MAJESTIES Commiſſioners Appointed to execute the Act for Settlement of <hi>IRELAND.</hi>
            </head>
            <p>WHereas by our late publiſhed Rules, Or<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ders and Directions, &amp;c. dated the two and twentieth of OCTOBER laſt paſt, To prevent the ſurprizal of any perſon for want of due notice when We intend to begin with any particular County, and that all perſons concerned in any of the Lands claimed by Innocents in ſuch County, may have certain notice of the perſons claim<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing the ſame: We have thought fit and ordered to begin with the ſeveral Claimants in the City and County of the City of DUBLIN, and to ſend forth our publick notice thereof to the ſeveral Counties throughout this Kingdom, with Liſts containing the Claimants Names and Denominations aſwel of the Lands claimed in thoſe particular Counties, as of Lands claimed in other Counties:</p>
            <p>Theſe are therefore to ſignifie unto all perſons con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cerned, That upon TUESDAY the tenth day of FEBRUARY next enſuing, We intend to ſit publickly in Court at the KINGS INNS DUBLIN, then and there to proceed to the hearing of ſuch of the undernamed Claimaints Cauſes, (a Liſt whereof is herewith ſent) as ſhall then, and ſo from time to time, be fitted and pre<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pared for our Adjudication, according to our ſaid publiſhed Rules, Orders and Directions, &amp;c.</p>
            <p>And We do further hereby ſignifie, That the ſaid under-named Claimants are hereby required to ap<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>point
<pb facs="tcp:136892:3"/> their Atturneys reſpectively to proſecute their Claims before Us.</p>
            <p>And all Souldiers, Adventurers, and other per<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſons whatſoever, concerned in any of the under-men<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tioned Lands, their Atturneys, Agents or Sollicitors, (who have been ſo remiſs and negligent in proſecuting their Claims, and bringing in their anſwers, that We could not hitherto proceed to the publick hearing of Cauſes, as We intended) are hereby likewiſe requi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>red to be more diligent in making their appearances, in filing their anſwers, and producing their Witneſſes, Evidences and other Writings, according to the re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſpective days and times, and at the peril by Us preſcri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bed in Our publiſhed Rules, Orders and Directions a<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>foreſaid.</p>
            <closer>
               <dateline>Given at the <hi>Kings Inns Dublin,</hi> 
                  <date>the 16th day of <hi>December,</hi> 1662.</date>
               </dateline>
               <signed>Signed by Order, THOMAS KENNEDY, Chief Clerk to the ſaid Commiſſioners.</signed>
            </closer>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="table_of_property_ownership">
            <pb n="1" facs="tcp:136892:3"/>
            <p>
               <table>
                  <row>
                     <cell role="label">Claimants Names.</cell>
                     <cell role="label">Denominations of the City, County of the City, &amp; County of DUBLIN.</cell>
                     <cell role="label">Other Counties.</cell>
                     <cell role="label">Denominations.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Angleſey Ar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thur Earl, and Walter Plun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ket.</cell>
                     <cell>7 Houſes.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Angleſey Ar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thur Earl, and Patr. Tallant.</cell>
                     <cell>5 Houſes in S. Brides ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Arthur John.</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes, waſte land. Carbery houſe in Skinner-row. 8 houſes and 24 acres of land. Hacketſtown. Pierſtown Lumlottery. A bond of the Staple of 400 <hi>l.</hi> A Bond of the Staple of 100 <hi>l.</hi> Neals-town, Weſtpelſtown.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                        <p>Roſcomon Mayo ‖ Louth: Roſcomon: Mayo and Sligo.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>The Rectory of Knock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mark: Heathſtown: Har<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riſtown: Drumine: New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rath: Mullagh: Curry: Drumcaſſil: Richards-town: Abby in Atherdee and Parks: Galy: Leo: Garran: Ballikilline: Drombofin, Dromoma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dery: Fullenlanker: Cluombuock: ‖ A bond of the Staple of 1000 <hi>l.</hi>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Allen Edward.</cell>
                     <cell>Several Houſes: Athgoe</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                        <p>Louth Wicklow</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Biſhopscourt: Oughte<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rard with the Rectory thereof: Painstown: Hartwelmill: Keelocks: Rathmore: Palmerſtown Little Rath: Atherdee Kilbride.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Archibald Pierce.</cell>
                     <cell>Two Houſes Clogheran, Swords Cappag, Killenardan</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Wicklow</p>
                        <p>Cavan</p>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Glaſinmullin, the Tiths of Brea, Ten poles of land and a Caſtle, Crikriagh, Latelow: Toniveagh, Maghery in Caltry, Knockitean, A<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ghatenevulty, Kiltily Benevulty, Leſderig Bogh, Aghigaſlan, Black<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hall, Several Statutes.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Arthur Patrick.</cell>
                     <cell>Two houſes, Colmans-town. Two Statutes for 400 <hi>l.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Allen Ralph.</cell>
                     <cell>Two houſes, one waſte plot of ground.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="2" facs="tcp:136892:4"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Arthur Bennet.</cell>
                     <cell>5 Houſes, One park in S. Keavans ſtreet, Iriſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, the wood of Caſtleknock.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                        <p>Tipperary</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Creiſtown, Kellyſtown, Newtown.</p>
                        <p>Annagh, Derry: Ballyurgane.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Aſh Rich. <hi>jun.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>1 Houſe in Highſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell>Kildare</cell>
                     <cell>The great Fernaght.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Archibald Chriſtofer.</cell>
                     <cell>One Stonehouſe in St. Patrickſtreet. Oldgrange, Brea. The Rectory of New-town in the Strand.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                        <p>Wicklow</p>
                        <p>Catherlagh</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Grangfort <hi>alias</hi> Grange foer, Collinstown <hi>al.</hi> Collins, Thorimſtown, <hi>al.</hi> Coninſtown, Coole<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rick, Huetſtown, Kilcae, Tymolinbey, S. Johns<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land: Inchmaquidder, Naas, The Rectory of Kilcrony, Killelade, Portreſs, Moylabby, Spretſtown Crookſtown Gurteen, Ivaughan, Da<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vidstown, Kilruſh, Tir<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>doyn, Solland, Johns<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Kill.</p>
                        <p>Ratool, Corriſtown, <hi>al</hi> Balliſhroe, Spinnans, Toberogan, Gracesland Gibbletstown, the Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctory of Fontsland, Glancar, Glancormack. Caſtledermot.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Archbald Ed<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ward.</cell>
                     <cell>Two houſes in Thomas<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, 2 in S. Kevan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, 2 Tenements at the Green.</cell>
                     <cell>Wicklow</cell>
                     <cell>Templecarrig</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Aylmer Ge<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rald.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Shipſtreet</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Siſly, Obreſtown, Mala<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fine, Balrath, Deens, Higginſtown, Carrick, Cruiſtown, Begnetshills, Bariſtown, Rectory of Ballimagarvey, Billards<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Seneſcalstown, Thirſtenſtown, Dunmo. Drogheda 2 houſes Hainstown, Reynoldstown, Gibstown, Carnonbreg, Preiſtland, Chanonrock Coolcredan, Dromcawel Monaſterbois.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="3" facs="tcp:136892:4"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Allen Law<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rence.</cell>
                     <cell>Three houſes in Wine<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tavern ſtreet, ſeveral houſes in S. Patrick<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, 2 houſes on Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chants key, A Feefarm in S. Nicolas pariſh with<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>out the walls, A Statute Staple of 200 <hi>l.</hi> A Sta<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tute Staple of 800 <hi>l.</hi> County Clantarf, Dalky.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                        <p>Sligo Queens Meath</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Richardstown, Poo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>haustown, Verdestown, Branganstown, Bergan, Maſhfieldstown, Rath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>eskin.</p>
                        <p>Dromcouragh <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Inch <hi>al.</hi> Ballycoolin <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Davistown, Corballies, Much-Roberstown.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Brown Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas.</cell>
                     <cell>Three houſes and a gar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>den, an Orchard and a park in S. Thomaſtreet, Clondalkin, Knock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>muckine, Venables farm, Lukan.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Bath Peter.</cell>
                     <cell>8 Houſes, Barbies land, Coolock, the troul-mill of Swords, S. Dowlagh, 40 acres betwixt Santry and Clunturk, Clun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>turk, A Statute Staple of 1000 <hi>l.</hi> on Athcarn, Richinhead, Hackes<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, A rent charge on Walter Cruce.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Roſcomon</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Grange end, Thomas town, the Grange of Trevet, the red moor <hi>al</hi> Dunſoghlin, A Statute Staple of 830 <hi>l.</hi> on the eſtate of G. Crofton.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Blake Patrick, and others.</cell>
                     <cell>4 Houſes, Rathcool, Taſſagart.</cell>
                     <cell>Galway</cell>
                     <cell>Gortigany, Killogene<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>malow, Killogecoſtraw, Gortincorra.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Barnwall Will. Mary his wife and Dominick Hughs.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe on Cockhill.</cell>
                     <cell>Weſtmeath</cell>
                     <cell>Mullingare.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Ball Thomas.</cell>
                     <cell>2 Houſes in Pipeſtreet 1 houſe in Highſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath Kildare</cell>
                     <cell>Bolton, Robinſton. Millston.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Bermingham Patrick.</cell>
                     <cell>One garden-plot in Ox<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>montown.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Brown Mabell.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Roſemary lane.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Beal Joſias and Barbara.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in S. Johns lane.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="4" facs="tcp:136892:5"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Bellew Edward</cell>
                     <cell>10 <hi>l.</hi> per annum out of William Higgins houſes and lands.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Bath Patrick.</cell>
                     <cell>2 Houſes and ſeveral other Tenements in Pipeſtreet and Mary lane, Glaſnevine.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>Balgeath.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Barnwal James</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes, Deum<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nagh, Tirenure, Camiſh, Gallan-town, Cromiſin, Ballimad, Ballibrigen, Balliformot.</cell>
                     <cell>Wicklow Louth</cell>
                     <cell>Tiniepark, Ardee.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Banks Andrew.</cell>
                     <cell>One meſſuage in High<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, 1 houſe in Skin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ner-row, 1 houſe in Highſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Barnwel Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bert.</cell>
                     <cell>2 houſes in Cookſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell>Mearh Wicklow</cell>
                     <cell>Clonmeath, Maſetown, Kilmakennock.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Bret John and others.</cell>
                     <cell>2 Houſes in Highſtreet. 1 houſe in Chriſtchurch lane.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Deece</hi> Barony Goltromer, Knockmark <hi>Ratooth</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Mixmal.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Brenan Ri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chard.</cell>
                     <cell>1 Houſe in S. Johns lane.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Brice Richard.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>1 Houſe in the Corn-market, 2 houſes in S. James ſtreet, 1 houſe in S. Thomas ſtreet, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mainam, 2 houſes in Newſtreet, Giffords grove, Flouds freehold, Fitzſimons or Bealings land, the Backey, the new park.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Hoſpital of S. John of Jeruſalem, Sloesland, Clinſhers park, Crumlin.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>Dunboyn</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Barnwel Mary.</cell>
                     <cell>1 Houſe in S. Thomas-ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="5" facs="tcp:136892:5"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Bor John.</cell>
                     <cell>2 Houſes in S. Michaels lane.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Galway</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Canmer, Ballimrergh, Garnaan, Balaghbane, Derrin, Laghlin, Tober<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kegh, Ballinderry, Ballagh, Cagail. Great Bewbeck.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Burnel Henry Eſq;</cell>
                     <cell>Houſes in Oxmontown, Iriſhtown, Lutterils<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Barbiſton, Caſtle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>knock, Blancherſton, Hartstown, <hi>al.</hi> Staheny, Coulock, Backiſtown, Caſtle-Curragh, A mill and weir in the Liffie, Ric<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kenhead, Diſwelstown, Kelliſtown, Clanſillagh, Finaghsland, Jannings land, Stagob, Porters<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Dillons land, The pace, Aſhtown, Carpenterstown,</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Moyfinragh</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Caſtle-Rickard, Ballinihan.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Salt</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Killiſtown, Creeſtown, Newtown, Grageſal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lagh, Powerstown, Kilmartin, Craſerath.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Barnwal Pa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>trick.</cell>
                     <cell>5 Houſes.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleek</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Kilmone, Primerſton, Rath, Iriſton, Ballihake Kilrew, Smithſton, Franckſton, Keaſer, Balliſton, Tough, Bodin Ratouth, Flemington, Mananſtown, Kinard, Hilton.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ratowth</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Moſenrath, Rathmolan, Treman, Stranne, Clon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>covan.</p>
                        <p>7 Houſes in Drogheda.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Birmingham Mary and Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ximilian Dem<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pſey &amp; Anne <hi>ux.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>The Fleece in Fiſh-ſhambleſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                        <p>Kings</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Carhery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Donferth, Diſert, Mu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>clan, Mulgigh, Killien, Ballinamallagh, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>murry, Kilſhanchoe, Irr, Ballrennet, Ballin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>derry, half Mucklan,</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Inkehy</hi> half Bar.</p>
                        <p>Ballicolgan, Laraghs.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="6" facs="tcp:136892:6"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Ball John.</cell>
                     <cell>11 Houſes and the ſhut clap-mill, Portrane &amp; the Rectory thereof.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleek</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Londerstown, New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town of Duleek, Bolton, Robinstown.</p>
                        <p>Milletstown.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Birne Daniel.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Several houſes and te<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nements.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtlknock</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Stagobby, Abbiſtown.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Wexford</p>
                        <p>Wicklow</p>
                        <p>Queens</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Shilmalier</hi> Barony.</p>
                        <p>Ardſmead, Collinstown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Arcklow.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballinecorbeg, Balli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>caple, Ballinclare, Carrigmore.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Portnelton.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Quintinally, Moret.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Stradbally.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Allebeg.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Bamber Roger &amp; Tereſa <hi>ux.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>One houſe in High<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, 1 houſe in S. Patrickſtreet.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nettercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Murtheree.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Lowth</cell>
                     <cell>Keappock, Brodlogh, Baltraſney, Miltown, Rath, Drommore, Capogs mill, S. Sundays land, Atherdee, Reco<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gnizance of 1000 <hi>l.</hi> ac<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>knowledged by Tho. Keppocks Recognizance of 200 <hi>l.</hi> from Gerald Cowley of Atherdee &amp; William Moor of Bar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>meath, Another Reco<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gnizance of 300 <hi>l.</hi> ac<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>knowledged by John Dowdal of Atherdee.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Barnwell James of Brimore.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>1 houſe on merchants Key, Brimore, Fle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mingstown, Newhaven, Moylaragh, Plunkets land.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrodery</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Balrothery, Balbrigan, Balſcaddan, Garreſtown, Tobergrag, Ballimad, Drimnagh.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>
                              <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>ppercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cruſrath, Little Sta<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>heny, Blancherſtown, Ringwellstown, Tyrrynure, Camadge.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dunboyn</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Peirſtown, Marſhal, Dunboyn, Newtown de Dunboyn, Brabſtown, Collierſtown, Black<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>wood, Hawkenstown, Warenſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleek.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Battranstown, Cock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ranstown, Boynanstown Denamstown, Pruins<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Racaſtown, The Grange of the Logh, S. Ganſtons, Duleek, Carblagh.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="7" facs="tcp:136892:6"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Ballyformant, Gallans<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Crumlin, Fox and Gooſe.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kells</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Kilmainam beg.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Margallen</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Oriſtown, Knock, Lyſhanſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Atherdee</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The chiefLord demeaſn and the meadow adjoy<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ning, the great hill of Atherdee, Mullaghdry<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lan, Mullaghmulin, Sta<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>killin.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Brown Dame Mary.</cell>
                     <cell>2 houſes on the blind Key.</cell>
                     <cell>Longford</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Moydo</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Bellamore, Caldragh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gebbedegh, Clontehe, Clonelan.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Barnwel Simon <hi>&amp; ux.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Five houſes in the Suburbs.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleek</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Kilmone, Brimerſton, Iriſhton, Rath, Balli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hack.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ratouth.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Kilbrew and the Advou<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſon of Kilbrew pariſh, Smithſton, Franckſton, Reaſle, Paliſton, Toagh Bodin, Ratouth, Flem<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mington, Grange end, Dunſaghlin, Mananſton, Kinand, Ulton.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Moyfenrath</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Raſhmolian, Troman, Little Stran.</p>
                        <p>7 houſes in Drogheda.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Crawley Edw.</cell>
                     <cell>3 houſes, Bellingstown, Kilcoskan, Great and little Bellingstown, Loghmartin.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                        <p>Monaghan</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ferrald</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cookstown, Athclare. Ballymeaghan.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Cheevers John.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>2 Houſes on the Wood-Key,</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrodery</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Garistown.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Skreen.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Maſtown, Corballis, Painſtown, Rogerstown Bodingham, Kilmoon.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Naas.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Rathmoor, Pounches<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Woolfstown, Haynſtown, Athgarret, Firhill, Skeogs,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="8" facs="tcp:136892:7"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Wicklow</p>
                        <p>Catherlagh</p>
                        <p>Wexford</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Philipstown, Ediſtown, Cradogstown, Balcaſe, Ballicane <hi>al.</hi> Plowland, Godamendy, Ramore<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mill.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Talbotstown</hi> bar.</p>
                        <p>3 Caſtles, Butlers court, Knockanem, Cnockerin, Cnocanore, Oldcourt, Monfin, Raturele, Cul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lenſhil, Balligore, Co<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>menſtown, Bollenſmut<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tane, Ballydangelly, both the loweſt: Cnock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>anybroky, Inchbane, Ballinetony, Bollynes<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kehanie, Ballynoltagh, the Kell of 3 Caſtles, Temanerly, Coſhana<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vally, Slewnelaraghduff, Slewſaw, Carrigletrim: Killincnappagh, Ballin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>foyl, Ballyſillore, Clono<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vally, Sknygane, mac-Nebantry, Carrigdown: Glanbride, Downfoord, 18 tenements and land in the town of Wick<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>low.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Catherlagh</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Grangefort: Littletown, Ballygory: Glenoge: Rathvern: Rathveren <hi>al.</hi> Rathverehan: Clin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>clogh <hi>al.</hi> Kingclogh: Moteleſſagh, Ballenſy<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neare, Banogboy: the tythes of Frierſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Bargie</hi> bar.</p>
                        <p>Ballyhaly, Ballylosky: the hill in the barony of Bargy, Horeſtown, Halſlone, Scurlogs buſh, Lecane, Deans caſtle, Grange, Graige, Balli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mader, Ballyfrorie, Banno, Duncormuck.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="9" facs="tcp:136892:7"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Shilmalier</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Coolrahin, Church<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Ballycollany, Ballear, Birdſtown, Sommerſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Fort</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Coſſenſtown, Balli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cnocane, Killalane, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>limenan, Ballyvouch, Ballyrely, Hayesland, Clongaddy, Roches, Keatings, Ballygrun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gan, Cloomeen, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rigechurch, Barriſtown, Kereaght; Iſland.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Cadowgan E<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liz. <hi>vid.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>One houſe on the Woodkey.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Chamberlain Roger.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Parſons<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lane.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Clerk John.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Swan-tavern in High<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, Five houſes and a waſte piece of ground in Oxmantown, Two houſes in Caſtleſtreet, Six houſes in S. Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas and S. James ſtreet, One houſe in S. Ste<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>phens ſtreet,</p>
                        <p>One judgment.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Tipperary</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dunhoyn</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Notſton, Rowan, Cra<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dockſtown, Loughſal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lagh, Bradſton, Main, Barrets place, Stephens place, Barons park, Philipſton <hi>al.</hi> Boolis, Kenaghſton, Purchers<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton, Curcoyn, Ball<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mucolly called Tues land, Nallswood, Go<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nocks, Warrenſtown, Mileſton, Muchfeild, Stockins, Walſheogrow, Lawkins, Pinkſtown, Ballipadine, Dunboyn, Dun aghlin, Clonee, Ronskeagh. One parcel of land.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Carrick Simon.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Highſtreet</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Carbery Richard.</cell>
                     <cell>One meſſuage by New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gate.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>Ballymagarvy.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="10" facs="tcp:136892:8"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Culm Debora <hi>vid.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Two houſes in Golden lane.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>Tarraghee <hi>al.</hi> Caſtleboy Cunnigar Farm Blakes<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>buſh, Thornton, Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rons meadow, Knock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gowran, Bodinſleys, Baronſleys, Skryne.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Coſgrave Matthew.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe on the Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chants key.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Coſgrave Laurence.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe on the Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chants key.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Crolly <hi>alias</hi> Chamberlin Thomaſin <hi>vid.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>16 houſes,</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Colock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Glaſnievin <hi>al.</hi> Dracots farm, Kilmainham.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Weſtmeath</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kells</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Chamberlinſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Lune</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Moyacher.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Mollengar</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Two houſes in Mollen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gar.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Cook Amy.</cell>
                     <cell>6 Houſes.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Cleer Patrick.</cell>
                     <cell>2 houſes in S. Thomas ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Coleman Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas.</cell>
                     <cell>A houſe, Orchard and garden in Newſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Chriſt-Church Dean and Cha<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pter.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>The Chantry lands of S. Annes Guild, S. Seths Guild, 3 houſes in Oxmontown, ſeveral houſes on the Wood<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>key, One houſe,</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>
                              <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>ppercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Smothscourt <hi>al.</hi> Simonscourt. Colcot and the Cony<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>burry <hi>al.</hi> Scald hills, Ballimore-Euſtace.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Caddle Robert</cell>
                     <cell>2 houſes in S. Patricks ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Carbery John.</cell>
                     <cell>Baggatrath <hi>al.</hi> Baggots<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>roth.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Conran Wal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>1 houſe in S. Thomas ſtreet.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrodery</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Courragh.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="11" facs="tcp:136892:8"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Crump Chri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtophar and o<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thers.</cell>
                     <cell>The horſe-pool and one houſe in S. Michans, Shallon, Danceſtown, Kilmainham, Rahine, The mill of Collotrath, &amp;c.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Delahide John.</cell>
                     <cell>2 Houſes, Iriſhtown, Phepoſtown, Rahinny and Corballis.</cell>
                     <cell>Wicklow</cell>
                     <cell>Rathmuck, Ballyogan, Rathſalcan, the Tythes of Aſhtown and Pells<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dunſany Lord.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>One houſe, the Pace, <hi>Caſtlknock</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Fullam.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Cavan</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Skreen.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Dunſany, Corballis, Cloony, Hilltown, Ulickstown, Oriſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dunboyn</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Garreſtown, Kenni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtown, Voldenſtown,</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleek.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Curraghstown, Erick, Tutrath, Oldcaſtle,</p>
                        <p>half <hi>Fower</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Fenner, Bolies, Drum<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lerry, Caſtletor, Creſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>drame.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kells</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballyhiſt, Corriſtown, one Tenement and a chiefry in Kells.</p>
                        <p>Great and little Glane, Tullaghmedan,</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Deece</hi> Barony</p>
                        <p>The Rectory of Kiltale, Scurlockstown, Phernock.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleruan</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Knocknevoy, Aghbrack and Lorganboy.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Clomayho</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Kilfacy, Crocovertuine, Corkloghan, Corfur<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>noy.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Claminghan</hi> Bellychan, Tulliboy, Aghnehsdern.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="12" facs="tcp:136892:9"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dowde Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>One houſe in High<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, 2 houſes in Schoolhouſe lane, One houſe in S. Patrickſtreet <hi>Nettercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Murdery, Dowds-Ca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bragh, Strawbelly.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleknock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Porterstown, Burſers-town.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Navan, Rathmory, Knock-Rickard, Mol<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>loghdryllen, Ballitraſny Broadlogh, S. Sundays land, Atherdee, Mil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lockſtown, Kildermot,</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Atherdee</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Huntſtown, Haghlam, Simonstown, Finway.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ferrard</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Melton, Rathdroni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mure.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dunboyn</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Clonee, Morrals land.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dutton John.</cell>
                     <cell>1 houſe in Bridgſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Deſmineere Lewis &amp; John.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in the Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chants Key.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dongan Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas.</cell>
                     <cell>Two Houſes in Wine-Taverne ſtreet, three houſes in the New-Roe.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Duffe Richard and Ux.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Eleven Houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Cooleck.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Kilmainham, Clontarfe. Collinſtown, Davanſ-ſtown, Balleforman.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Deveniſh James.</cell>
                     <cell>Five Tenements called Horſemarket.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Deey Michael.</cell>
                     <cell>Eight Houſes.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dongan Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam, Lord Viſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>count.</cell>
                     <cell>The Park without Saint James, Stayne near the Colledge four Houſes. Dalky, Abbotſtown, the Rectory and Tithes of Palmers-town.</cell>
                     <cell>Kildare.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Salt.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Caſtletown, Kildrought, Moretown, Kilmarre<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dock, Godfrey-Harris<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton, Coolmac-Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas, Collinbacks-town, Poſſicks-town, Ardreſſe, Bebus.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Naas.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Shearlocks-town, with the moyety of the tithes <hi>Clare.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Clare, Cooledriny.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Salt.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The impropriate tithes</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="13" facs="tcp:136892:9"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Longford</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Queens</p>
                        <p>Kilkenny.</p>
                        <p>Catherlagh</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>of Kildrought.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Killeullin.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Tobberrogan, Johns<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Salt</hi> half Bar.</p>
                        <p>Killmean, Gibbins-town, Moretown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Clare.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Corrihils, Kilbegges, Long-town, Ballymany.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kannell.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Grange-Clare.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Clare.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Corrickeragh, the im<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>propriate tithes of Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>begg.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Connell.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The Tithes of Grange-Clare.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Clare.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The tithes of Corcke<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ragh, Stabbers-town, &amp; Hodgeſtown.</p>
                        <p>Ballineſheegard, Cooly<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vore.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kells.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballybreagheny, Gibs-town, Donagh-Patrick, Korbins-town.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Deece.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The impropriate tithes of Moyglare.</p>
                        <p>Rathnemanagh, Knoka<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>negrough, Coolcorin, Balliteighin, Knockan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>derry, Mariborogh.</p>
                        <p>The tithes of Temple Michael, Cool-Sarskan and Monegan.</p>
                        <p>The half of the tithes of Cloedagh, the half of the Rectory of A<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thade.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Sleward</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The tithes of the Baro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ny of Sleward.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>
                              <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>pper Ormond.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The impropriation of Middlethird, the im<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>propriation</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="14" facs="tcp:136892:10"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Catherlagh</p>
                        <p>Tipperary.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>of S. Johns town, <hi>alias</hi> Scadans and the tithes.</p>
                        <p>The tithes of Kilkenny<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>begg, Lyſmayneny, Liſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>necloanta, Garrinemo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>na, Liſnemorragh, Gort<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nemoddah.</p>
                        <p>The impropriation of Luchoe, Rathneganna<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nagh, Cleofadda, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rigigown, Barnedirge, Cloughurdan, Lough<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>anatteney, Ball riſtenna, Tiwel, Balliduffe, Sheraghquillagh, Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dine, Lisbally, Rath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nerenra, Liſſervan, Camſheceragh, Gort<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>more, Roſs-Reilcerrin, Liſludican, Ballidaggan, Liſſduffe, Ballyriskard and Knockna.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Doyn George</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Damaſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell>Downe.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Donag-Clony, Moyga<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nan, Ballykeele, Ballya<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ghreskiugh, Moyree.</p>
                        <p>Upper Bar. of <hi>Tuugh.</hi> Bawn and Dullany.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtlereagh.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballynehatty and Bally vnlvally.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dowde Chri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtopher.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Cook-ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dowdal Wal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe and Garden in Oxmantown, one houſe in S. Jame-ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Lune.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Athboy.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Halfoor.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Outfolk, <hi>alias</hi> Outhale.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kells</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Crievagh.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Lime.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Culconun, upper Bar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vecon.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kells.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Deamers-town, Griſh-town.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="15" facs="tcp:136892:10"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dowdal Ste<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>phen.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe near New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gate, one houſe in Corn-market, one on the Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chants key.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleek</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Gallanſtown, the little Boolies, the ſmall farm, Kenock, both the Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nes, Gaskranſtown, the Deems.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Skreen</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>The fourty Acres, two houſes in Duleek.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Farrard</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Terfeighan, Dunnany &amp; Corſtown, Dales and Kilcloghes, Callan, ſe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>veral houſes, Coolpark and other lands in Dro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gheda.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dungan Dame Mary.</cell>
                     <cell>Four houſes in Fiſham<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ble ſtreet, Parils, Stain, Dalkey, The Rectory &amp; Tithes of Palmerſtown, Abbotstown.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Queens</p>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Longford</p>
                        <p>Kilkenny</p>
                        <p>Catherlagh</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Rathnemanagh, Knock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>negrough, Coultoryne, Ballyteigerine, Knock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>enderry, Mariborough. Caſtletown, Kildraught, Moortown, Collen-blackſtown, Godfryhar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riſtown, Bebus, Sher<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lockſtown, Carryſhills, Kilbegs, the tithes of Longtown, Ballimany, Grange, Clare, Corcke<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ragh and the tithes, Kilmelridock, Coul mac Thomas, Poſſicks<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Ardreſs, the tithes of Stablerſtown, Hodgeſtown and Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>drogh.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kells</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Norbinſtown, the tithes of Moyglare, Gibſtown, Donaghpatrick, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>breaghwene.</p>
                        <p>The tithes of Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neſegard &amp; Culivore.</p>
                        <p>The tithes of Temple-micheal, Coolforckan and Mongany.</p>
                        <p>The tithes of Cloydagh S. Johnstown, Kilken<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nisbeg and Limoyneary,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="16" facs="tcp:136892:11"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Tipperary</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>the Rectory and tithes of Athad.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>
                              <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>pper Ormond.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Liſnecloonta, Goryne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mona, Lynemoragh, Gortnemudagh and Middlethreed.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Lower Ormond.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Lorchoe, Rathue, Gan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nanagh, Cleofadan, Cor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rigigowen, Barnedirge, Cloghurdan, Loghane<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>attyunvy, Balliſtinny, Tywell, Ballyduffe, She<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nagh, Quillogh, Rodine, Lisbally, Rath-mac-Ke<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nan, Liſſeynan, Camſe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ragh, Gortmore, Roſſe, Bealcarrin, Liſludican, Reilydaggin, Liſduffe, Balyrickard, Knockenae,</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Sleward.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Slevord.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dillon Luke.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Three houſes and lands,</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtlknock,</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cappock, Blanſhers<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Cardiffs and the new Mills and Killmar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>martin.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nettercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Finglas, Johns-town and the Boding.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Blundels-town, Kilma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>talway, Cromlyn, Coulecoat.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coolock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Killigh.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Lowth</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Two houſes and a Mea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dow in Drogheda.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ferard.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Dillons-land.</p>
                        <p>Betagh-town, and other lands.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Enos Mary.</cell>
                     <cell>A houſe in High-ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Eaſtwood John</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in S. Nicho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>las-ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Euſtace James.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Eighteen Acres in the Pariſh of S. James, 26 Houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleknock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Damaſtown, Maistown,</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Five houſes in Dro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gheda.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Salt.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Confye, Newtown, Bals<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cot, Howes-land Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>garee.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="17" facs="tcp:136892:11"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Corſtown, Ballycaeke.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ballruddry.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Balredry.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Rathcool, Taffagard, Clondalkan, Black<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>homehill.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Radown uppercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Dawkey, Dowdings<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Luckan.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ballruddry.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Calcott.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dunboyn</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Milestown, Rathlick.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Flemming John</cell>
                     <cell>Three houſes and a waſte piece of ground in Oxmantown, three houſes in Sautry.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fyan Francis</cell>
                     <cell>Sixteen houſes in S. Francis-ſtreet, one houſe in Corn-Market.</cell>
                     <cell>Louth</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Droghe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>da.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fitz Symons Henry</cell>
                     <cell>Three houſes in Cook<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, one houſe near Newgate, one houſe in Backlane.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Finleys Mary</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>The third part of ſix houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Neithercroſs</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Murtherie.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Louth</cell>
                     <cell>Keappocke, Brodlogh, Baltraſwry, Miltown, Rathdrummore, S. Sundays land, Capotkes-Mill and 14 houſes, the third part of a Mort<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gage of a 1000 pounds upon Thomas Keppocks eſtate of Atherdie, the third part of a Mort<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gage of 300 l. upon John Dowdal of Ather<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>die, a third part of 200 pounds upon Gerrard Cowly of Ardy, and William More of Bar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>meth.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Frayne Red<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mond</cell>
                     <cell>Two houſes in S. Fran<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cis-ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Rathcourath.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Mullenmichan, Icheny<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>aday.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="18" facs="tcp:136892:12"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Moyahill.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Molingard.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Fartullagh.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Carrick, Carrickfrayne, Oulanſtown, Mahans<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Farbils.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Porters-town, Dar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>diſland, Killucken, Rathwyre.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Flemming Garret.</cell>
                     <cell>Two houſes in Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas-ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Cavan.</p>
                        <p>Moneghan.</p>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Fermanagh</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Clank.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Taghart, Dromhalp, Dingan, Dromaller, Tollibrick, Corlea, Liſenamneagh, Moher, Corneſaw, Capnaugh, Corwillis, Edendo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gullan, Dowae, Laragh, Drombarr, Moagh, Mollaghnercrea, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>leaghly, Corhalman, Cormay, Liſneſaſenagh, Coremery, Cortoberr, Corvaddy, Liſnarlare, Killbegge, Cabragh, Corrigirry, Eneskea, Moybolg, the impro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>priate tithes of Killane, Cnockbridge, Moybo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>logg, Templeport.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleraighdown.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Magherendown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dartry.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Toughreah, Tatecacke, Corſlea, Cortreen.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Atherdee</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Laganwater, Tullie, Newtown, Cormortine, Greatwood.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kells</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Emlagh, Mary-Abbey.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Demifore.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Corbally, Derreherri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dan, Grangestown, Cnockanvilry, Kilragh, Emlagh, Caſtleraigne, Lergan, Muntes.</p>
                        <p>The impropriate tithes</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="19" facs="tcp:136892:12"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Letrim.</cell>
                     <cell>of Kinally and Killert. The impropriate tithes of Clanclare, Killaſter and Moynally.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fitz Gerald Patrick.</cell>
                     <cell>Two hoſes in Mary Lane.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Kildare.</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Clane.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Clane.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Clane.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ikeathy.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Oughter.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Inny.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Kilmurry.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Salt.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ardreſſe.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dunboyn</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Clony.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fitz Simons James</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Three houſes in the Wood Key.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Callaghtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Swords.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Swordes, Rogans-town, Battlepark.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Foſter James</cell>
                     <cell>Six houſes in Francis-ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fullam Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Caſtle-ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fingall Earl Luke</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>A houſe in Oxman<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrothery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Reynolds-town.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Cavan.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleraghan.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cloghwelly, Getragh, Cloghwellyetrach, Cloghurgool, Liſſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nalany, Drumgore, Cor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nuſlee, Cargach, Dru<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nane, Bare, Virginia, Clanmore, Richardrom, Balleene, Carnehuesky, Killikeene, Liſlea, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gach, Enagh, Thar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tach, Liſlurty, Eden<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>burt, Logh-Ramer, Portan, Gallon-mac-Geroge, Eterand, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gach, Carrick, Athy<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hencruagh, Munin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chocan, Knockatam<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pal, Tineden, An<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chonquilly,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="20" facs="tcp:136892:13"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Eaſtmeath.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Corronagh, Knocknegartan, Agen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tegall, Ballahdorragh, Iſland, Knocknefea, Barnagh, Lurganboy, part of Knocknofea, Gallonfieragh, Gallon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtramore, Galloniteragh and Gallonſtramore, Aghecullen, Keallreagh, Moet, Croſſeighan, Aghedowan, Outeragh, Carrigeagh, Pollgariffe, Lacarowihill, Edenco<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>niſhian, Shandrom, A<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ghemore, Cloonmago, Fry, Neid, Knockowny, Cooletwoe, Pollyteden, Aghonehae, Galloaroe, Galloncourtampull, Knocklahan, Aghe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>brack, Lorganboy, Poll<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>naſhye, Liſſinaghan, Downamolloge, Knock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>anroe, Liſſedonnelan, Aghoncheadgotah, Lor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>geragh, Skarenhien, Tomquill, Omery, Killoge, Mulianeſhana<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>clone, Agheneden.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleraghan.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ardskea, Clontraſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fane, Deherny, Lemne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neſſe, Carrigneveagh, Culemoney, Ne Carri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bruſe, Fertaghow, Fer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tagheghtra, Aghen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dronge, Napertune, Loghrawie, Agheler, Killegnemore.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ratooth.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Growtoran <hi>al.</hi> Groves<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land, Rayes-town, Foyls-town part. Rathre<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gan, Liſmachon, Ribes-town, Parſons-town, Porre-town, Wood<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land, Tillikilliconner, Beleams-town, Little</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="21" facs="tcp:136892:13"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fingall Earl Luke.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>and mickle Derricks, Clonroſſe, Swyocks-town, Drumnineere, Dunſaghlin, Creemore, Dunſhaghlin, Ardca, La<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dyhill.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Halfore.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Killalan, Gechans-town, Galboys-town, Seraghs-town, Tonlegaith, Coreſtown, Old caſtle, Caſtle Corr, Croſdrum <hi>alias</hi> Faſſagh, Glanca, Baltraſny, Hamlings-town, Newtown, Gi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>verveamon, Rath, Cor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riſton.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dunboyn.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Part Bellandy, Foyles-town, New Bracetown, Balliantry, Nottſtown, Little Bally mac Colly, Kennanſtown, Dun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>boyn.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kells.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Killsby, Nillinaghs-town, Mills-town, Cul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>linſtown, Boltown, Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bertſtown, Drumbar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rugh, Deſtinrath, Cal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liaghtown, Maprath, Curragh, Clunfenan, Corneſaſe, Mote, Ra<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thenrick, Loghan, Ca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bragh, Scurlocks land.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Deece.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Tulloghmeaden, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tayle, part Boyeſttown, Knockmack, Morestown Bedfadſtown, Bollog<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bane.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Skreene.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Walterſtown, part Cul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>veſtown, Killeene, Clowanſtown, Smiths<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Berelſtown, Dwogſton.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Navan.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Tullaghanoge, Courts-town, Moniſtown,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="22" facs="tcp:136892:14"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Weſtmeath.</p>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meadſtown, Tulchans<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, adjacent towns, Little Bellardan.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Fore.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Raherkin, Hartſtown, the Rectory of Kilskyer.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Slaven.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Fegenſtown part, Swylefield.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Delvyn.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Legſhiny.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Fore.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Glanydon, Carrack, Carrack, Martins-town, Ballimiowen, Arkiſtown. A houſe in Drogheda.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Foſter John</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Six houſes and a Brew<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>houſe in St. Francis ſtreet, Two in St. Mi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chaels Lane.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Ballidowde, Esker, I<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riſh town, Lucan.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Weſtmeath.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Deece.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Kilgrage, Peirſtown, Porterſtown, Bayſtown,</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ratoth</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Dunſaghlin.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ktlkenny</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>The Rectory of Drum<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ram.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fitz Simons Marcus</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>A houſe in New-ſtreet, Two other houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrodery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballmadrought, Cor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>duffe.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>
                              <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>ppercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Rathcool, Dalky, New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Colmanſtown, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>more, Taſſagard.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Kildare</cell>
                     <cell>Caſtle Dermot.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fyan Edmund</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes in Col<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ledge Green, and a houſe in Corn-market, a houſe in Winetavern ſtreet, and a houſe in Bride<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fitz Williams William, and Alice his wife</cell>
                     <cell>Two parts of the Pre<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cinct of S. John Baptiſt without New gate, three Mills and and a Garden, a houſe &amp;c. in Back<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lane,</cell>
                     <cell>Wicklow</cell>
                     <cell>Rahinclag, Ballogh, Shallon, Benettſtown, Trablie, Ratouth, Fin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nor, Millhill, Duleeke, Walterſtown, Salimoor,</cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="23" facs="tcp:136892:14"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>a houſe in Ram<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lane, a houſe in Cook<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, a houſe in Corn<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>market.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>County.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Clonſhillagh, with the Rectory and Grange, Skirmullin <hi>alias</hi> Tir<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mullin, Fibleſtown, Barnegeeth, Janings land <hi>alias</hi> James land, Fenaghs land, Miſtel<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſton, Godamendy, Huntſtown, Brune <hi>alias</hi> Rohernebrune, Cole<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>manſtown, Loghton, Tobberbin, Baldovan, Colecot, Fedanſton, Esker, Ballowne, Flock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>meadow, Rohnicallagh, Brandonſgrow, Kille<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>agh, Owenſtown, Law<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>renſtown, Vallanſtown, Great Stokeing.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Orsborns land, Mab<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſton, Curtlagſton, Go<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nogkeſton, Rathleeke, Mognelſwood, Ballama<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>colly, Maſtockſtown, Haughingſton, Roet<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſton, Priſton.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fagan Criſto<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pher Eſq;</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>A houſe and a Caſtle-in Corn-market, two-Tofts in Cook-ſtreet, and a waſte piece of ground, two houſes on Wood-key, one houſe in Fiſhamble ſtreet, one houſe in S. Michaels lane, ſix houſes, &amp;c. in Oxmantown, two houſes in S. Patrick<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, ſix houſes in Sheepſtreet, two houſes in Wine-tavern ſtreet, a houſe in Skinner rowe, two houſes in Bridge<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, Caſyes tower on Wood-key, Aſh-park or Combe-park, &amp;c.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>County.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Feltrim, Mabeſtown, Effernock, Clongel, Drynam and Hamons<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>towne, Stacoule, Kin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſaly,</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Wexford</p>
                        <p>Sligo.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Morgallen.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Drakeſtown, Williams<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Mountainſtown, the Grange.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kells.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cullcomman Kells, Mullaghegh Kells.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ratouth.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cullcomman.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ballagheene.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Killgowne, Ballybane, Ballyhought, Ballinte<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gert, Tinekilly, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dovenell, Tobbernenan.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Tirrerill.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballynaſhee, Rathduffe, Tillinure, Caſhell <hi>alias</hi> Caſhelnebuny, Carrow Geoltie, Carrow Iclean, Umerirow, Carrow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vickiſſook.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Carran.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Carrowardcoran, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>onachan, Carrowknock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>choirke,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="24" facs="tcp:136892:15"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>S. Doughlags, Bo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>huner and Ballmacartie with the tithes, &amp;c. the Rath of Killofferie with the Rectory and tithes, Effernock, the great tithes of Balgriffin.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The upper Mill, Rath-cool.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Rathdowne.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Bloyke, with the great and ſmall tithes and cu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtoms, Dalkey and the tithes of Dalkey, and Brenanſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrodery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The Curragh, Darcis<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Loughſhenny, Thomaſtown, Tan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kardſtown, Donabate, Palmerſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleknock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Newtown, Rathcool, Cromline.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>
                              <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>ppercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Upper mill, Cromlin.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nethercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Luske.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Carrowdan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>clonagh, Carrowknock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>choilme, Carrowknock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rawer, Leaghskeagh.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Farrel Ed<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mond and o<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thers</cell>
                     <cell>Two houſes.</cell>
                     <cell>Louth</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Atherdee.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Painſtown.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fitz Rery Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bert</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>One houſe in S. Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas ſtreet.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle</hi> Bar.</p>
                        <p>Colletrath, Sprickles<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Gallanſton, Cor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>reſtown, Chappel Mid<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>way.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ratouth.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Greeneg.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fox Gear<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rot and Elinor his wife</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>The Caſtle of the Cran,</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>two houſes in Caſtle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>County.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cromblin.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Weſtmeath.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Rathcourath.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Moyvoore, Temple Patrick, Loggenegall, Ballinecurrie, the five Acres.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="25" facs="tcp:136892:15"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Killkenny.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The impropriate Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctories of both the Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>skins.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kerbery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The Grange, Ballnial<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lacke.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fitz Gerald George</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                        <p>Weſtmeath.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Moyfenragh.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Tycrahan, Kilarde, Ballyboggan, Clonards, Harriſtown, Ballinekill <hi>alias</hi> Woodtown, Knoc<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kanegolly Park, Killoſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>billin, Cappaghvoggan, Baltogeny, Kilnecla<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nagh, Kilnegatlagh, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>murry, Kilmir, Donoer, Inſimore, Rathinally, Woodtown, Rathclony, Ardnemullan, Tou<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>laght, Aghnegullagh, Kilvarding, Balline<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>barne, Annagh, Moy<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>drum, Enan.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Lune.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Baltonoran, Ballinne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bracky, Ballinegulſy, Portleſter, Parkeſtown, Croſſanſtown, Moyfe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>char, Ballyver, Much<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>wood, Coleronan, Woodtowne weſt, Cor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ballis, Rathkenan, Rath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cormack, Moyrath, San<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>toe, Cluny.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Carbry.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Kilrumurry, Ballyowne, Ballinekill, Dirrinligg.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Forbill.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Canagad, Clontrave, Munganſtown, Griffins<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Aneskenan, Der<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rymore, Bruttenſtown, Chananſtown, Jo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>viſtown, Priſtown, Pa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>getts Park, Mileſtown, Creggſtown, Rathfarne. Cloghanſtown, Fores<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="26" facs="tcp:136892:16"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Kings.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Clonycullin, Ball<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>royne, Griffinſtown, Ra<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hintull, Kerinſtown, Kilpatrick, 7 l. <hi>per an.</hi> out of the Earl of Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dares land in Farbill, Corballis, Poſlickſtown Ballintlevy, Ballintor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nan, Croughoule, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>croughoule, Glan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>more, Coyne, Mr. Gawlyes lands, Carnes, Knockmant, Banachir, Sarſwelſtown, John Duffs town, Corbets<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Ballindeny, Gnewbane, Killinure, Ballyneclagh.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Moyaſhill.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Newtown, Spittlehouſe, Ardmornes, Corri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>naghir, Rahincorrick <hi>al.</hi> Suircan and Corboge.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Clonlonan.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Upper Clonlonan wood, Clonaltron wood and other parcels, Knoc<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kinea.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Moyaſhill</hi> and <hi>Magha<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rederon.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Pettits wood, and a houſe in Molingare, Clonykivant, Rath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>wyre, Killucan.</p>
                        <p>Coronellor, Philips<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Lihince.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Gilbert Sir George</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Bridge<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Gough An<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thony</cell>
                     <cell>Two houſes, a mort<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gage of 70 l. on two houſes in S. Michaels lane, the Pill in Ox<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mantown.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Wicklow</p>
                        <p>Tipperary.</p>
                        <p>Kildare.</p>
                        <p>Downe.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>The Rectory of Arkloe with the tithes.</p>
                        <p>The Rectory of New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Lenan, with the tithes.</p>
                        <p>Eight or nine Tene<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ments in Kill.</p>
                        <p>Ardagh, Donowan, Dromcroe, Ballyawn,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="27" facs="tcp:136892:16"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Mahirmorghie, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>attine, the two Dirricks, the two Mondoraghes, Molederthan, Glaſtrym.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Gernon Ni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cholas</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Gough Igna<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tius</cell>
                     <cell>Eight houſes and Te<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nements, Sarkes, Par<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kes, Glaſnivin, Why<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>leſtown, Hayeſtown, Balldongan, Ballinſton, Hutton.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Glover John</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>One houſe in Newroe.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Sagard.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Graham Haure</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Two houſes with two Backſides, two houſes upon the Key.</p>
                        <p>Garreſtown.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                        <p>Wicklow</p>
                        <p>Wexford</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Macetown.</p>
                        <p>Paunchtown, Wooleſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Rathmore, Payneſtown, Athgarret. Part Grange.</p>
                        <p>Ballihally, Balliare, Caſſenſtown, Bridſtown, S. Margarets, Famers<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Balliknockane.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Gough Willi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>am</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>A houſe in S. Francis ſtreet, a houſe in High<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, five Houſes in S. Michaels lane, a houſe on Wood-key, ſeveral houſes without Pole<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gate, a houſe in Skin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ners Rowe.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balredry.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Sutton, Redmonds farm, Balldungan, Whiteſtown and Hayes<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Longford</p>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Farrar.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Martinſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dundalke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cnockgoe.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ardie.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Stermanſtown, New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Mollaſtown, Liſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ranny, two houſes in Drogheda.</p>
                        <p>Daviſtown, Moretown, Malagha.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Gruill.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Taghimy, Killincarra. Kill.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Gibbons Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Two houſes, and two plots of ground in Ox<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mantown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coolock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Kilbarrock.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleknock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballyboggan.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Deece.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Paddinſtown and Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>maſtown.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="28" facs="tcp:136892:17"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Hamilton Sir Francis</cell>
                     <cell>Nine houſes.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Hicky William</cell>
                     <cell>Twelve houſes.</cell>
                     <cell>Weſtmeath.</cell>
                     <cell>Fininſland.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Holmes Peter</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Three houſes and a Horſe-mill.</p>
                        <p>Cloghranſwordes.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleek.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Kerreſton.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Higgin Francis</cell>
                     <cell>Five houſes and a plot of ground.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Handcock Chriſtopher</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Ten houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nethercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Clandalkin, Taſſagard, Swordes.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Kildare.</cell>
                     <cell>Rathmore, Mergetts<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Harding Philip</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in High-ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Holmes Simp<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſon</cell>
                     <cell>Two Parks and two water-mills, neer Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas court wood.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Hicky William</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in the Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chants key.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Hurley John</cell>
                     <cell>Two houſes in S. James ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Humphrey Joan, <hi>alias</hi> Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lew, Patrick mapas and o<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thers.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleeke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Clareſtown.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Hewlett George, and Mary <hi>
                           <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>x.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Oxman<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Hore Mary, Margaret and Alſon</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>One houſe on the Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chants key, two houſes in High-ſtreet, two houſes in Cook-ſtreet, Two houſes in S. Brides ſtreet, two houſes in Newrowe, ſeveral houſes in S. Francis-ſtreet, ſeveral houſes in S. Mary Abbey.</p>
                        <p>Kilſalgham, Domnuck, Coolcoyes, Corſtown,</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Wexford.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Clatterſton, Bulſton, Caleſton, three houſes.</p>
                        <p>Baller, Maſhall, Riſhalls, Hariſtown, Skal, Riſh, Kildowan, the Dirrtra, Criſtown, Grang-Sal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lah, Polhore, Caſtell-hills, Tammon.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="29" facs="tcp:136892:17"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Thomtown, the Rath, Bulkhale, Bedfords, Stradbally, great King<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſton, Rathla Caſtone, Leythill, Luske, Caſtle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>knock, Iriſhtown, Har<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riſtown, Rickinhead, Caſtle Carroaght.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Hamble John</cell>
                     <cell>A houſe in S. Nicholas ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleeke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballymadde, Smiths<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Gillinſtown, Corballis, Duleeke.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ferrard.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>A houſe in Drogheda, a houſe in Fermonfecuin.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Harris Edward</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes in Fiſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>amble-ſtreet, 2 houſes near S. Owens Church, two other houſes, and two parks near St. Ke<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vins. One houſe and a plot of Ground in Cooksſtreet. One other in Caſtleſtreet, The Town of Portra<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                           <desc>•</desc>
                        </gap>e.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Bar. <hi>Duleeke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Newtowne, Lander<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtowne.</p>
                        <p>Bar. <hi>Moyfenra.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Clunguffin.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Irving David and Ann Ux.</cell>
                     <cell>2 Houſes.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Jans Edward.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Two houſes and Gar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dens in Glaſmaquinock near Oxmontown, 2 ſmall meadow Parks, one great houſe in St. Michaels lane, one houſe in Winetavern ſtreet, one houſe in St. Patrick ſtreet, two houſes in St. Nicholas-ſtreet, Three houſes in Rochell-lane, 3 houſes in St. Georges lane.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The great and little Farm of Kilmaynham.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Weſtmeath.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleeke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Shallon, Kilkarvan, Prineſtown, Batram<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtowne. The mill of Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>beard, houſes in <hi>Duleek,</hi> the Abby of Skryne, Cuſacks-hall with parks, houſes in Skryne, Thorneton, Loghtown, Baldoghnan.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Rathconraght.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballimore.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Corkery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The Abby of Monti Feonan with a mill.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="30" facs="tcp:136892:18"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Jans Michael and Frances Ux.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe near New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gate, one houſe in Corne-market, one houſe on the Merchants Key.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath.</p>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleeke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Galſtown, the little Boolies, Small Farm, Kenock, the moyety of both the Carnes in Duleeke, Gaskianſtown, Deemes, two houſes in Duleek.</p>
                        <p>Terfeaghan with many houſes, dales, and part of Kilclogher, Callan.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Farrard.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Dunnany.</p>
                        <p>One houſe and garden in Deerſtreet, one houſe in Batchelors lane, eight acres of land in the Franches, one park in Green-Bater, two crofts without the gates, one Orchard without S. Lawrence gate, and a meſſuage in Batchelors Lane with ſeven walls and a Garden, and a Tenement in Heirs lane, one houſe in S. Johns ſtreet and a gar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>den, one ſhop with a chamber, one houſe in S. Peters ſtreet, one park, two houſes, one half of a meadow, one houſe in Batchelors lane.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kenneday Wal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter, George Uſher and John Walſh</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe. Taſſagard.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath.</cell>
                     <cell>Nottſtown, Rowan, Bradiſtown, Lough<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſallagh, Cradockſtown, Maynebarretts place, Stephens place, Barrons park, Philips town <hi>al.</hi> Boolies, Kennaghts<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Pincherſton, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>coyne, Balleneolly, Nalliwood, Warrinſton, Gonock, Milleſtown, The Much-fields, Stoc<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kens, Walſheſgrow,</cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="31" facs="tcp:136892:18"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Kildare</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Lamkins, Pinckleſtown, Dunboyn, Dunſaghlyn, Clony.</p>
                        <p>Lexlip.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kearny Ed<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mund</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in S. Patrick<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Corke.</p>
                        <p>Coſmee.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Conrey.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Garrihinagh <hi>al.</hi> Kill<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>more, Tonneregigh, Monnimore, Rahingh, Killbegg, Bealtra, Gort<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nacruſſy, Templetryen, Garreſtown, Gortni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cruſſy.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Carake.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballany.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Limricke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Gortgare, Schoule.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kildare, Went<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth Earl</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Kildare houſe, 1 houſe in S. Michaels lane, one garden and an Orchard near the Caſtle, S. Ste<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>phens Hoſpital, and the lands to the ſame be<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>longing, the tithes of the lands of the houſe of the hogs, Mintions mantle, &amp;c. Clondalkin, the Rectory of Gracedew, Tippkenin.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>In Com. Dublin</hi> or Wicklow.</p>
                        <p>Kilconut, Templecar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gie, Shebela, Killinure, Moyliſty, Moyskeagh, Mynore, Ballyellis, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lalig and half the Goule, Cremeſellin.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Catherlagh</p>
                        <p>Cavan.</p>
                        <p>Lymerick.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Kinnagh, Tonnegrohe, Barkill, Ballycaſlune, and Dowganſtown.</p>
                        <p>Aghtryde, Gary-Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bert, Croſrath, Poll<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kill, Pollrath, Clone<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tedaffe, Rahinmore, Rathclaghagh, Garyſal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lagh, Conline, Dro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mard, Callaghnegh, Aghtilmore, Lowagh <hi>al.</hi> Lodagh, Ballene<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>croſs, the mannor of Clonmahone.</p>
                        <p>Glaſchony, Killane<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>weary, Ballinfryory, Drommeyne.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coſmore.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Acleckagh, Brittal, Cor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kincolrone, Liſhmo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>reen, Peacke, Adare and ſeveral Burgeſſes, &amp;c. Cragane, Sallene and Farranna, Pallicy, Gar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rytullane, Garrypooky, Garrineportriffe, Caſtle Robert, Bantageara, Garranabrickene, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>laghnegerah, La<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ghughne ſporteenagh, Gurteenebalanaha,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="32" facs="tcp:136892:19"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kildare, Went<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth Earl of</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Keapacraheene, a parcel of paſture land, Gar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ryannony, Rathnawi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tagh, Ballyacarraney, Ballyvodane, Ballywil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly, Heighragh, Ardefi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>one, Liſavill, Bohuran<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>usky, Ballynabnoly, Garryanpookey, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſheoondehey, Killegno<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſy, Mollane, Gortganiffe, Gortaknochane, Garke<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>more, Balleaguoſſy, Ballynaſwagh, Ballykea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ling.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coſmore.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Lower, Gleananore, Be<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>abas, Rathmore, Do<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nenamanie and Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>traſtane, Ballynahow, Pollagh, Kearhowe, Ballymacrorie, Doone<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kippe, Ballymickane, Cloncallane, Caſtle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kippnie, Rahen, Ure<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gare, Ballyſtonymore, Ballyſtonybegg, Ballyn<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>curreyo, Ballywillen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>begg, Kearhowreagh, Ballyany, Coskenydedy, Criggane, Clounſhane.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kerry.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Claghrane, Ballylong<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fort.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Poblebryen.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The Iſland of Corka<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>more.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Connollagh.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Liſhduffe, Finterſtown, and Garraneard.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coſmay.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Tullorvey, White Ab<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bey, Black Abbey, Poor Abbey, Gortnadoghny, Gortnegea, Bollybally, Bonefion, Park more, Feranboy, Garryone, Girtenan, Varmſculla, Feleſteene, Ballycul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>leene,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="33" facs="tcp:136892:19"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kildare, Went<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth Earl</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Cloghrane, Tullo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vine, Ballenta, John Leas Dolloe, Maurice Fitz Geralds Dolloe, Ruſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſels Curagh Ineanoge. Thorntons Curraghine<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>oge, Tuoreene, Shan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>clonin, Skeaghmerry<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>geoge, Rathbrenagh, Ballenfryora, Creaff<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>begg, Croomegleab<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land, Rosſtemple, Ga<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>raneroe, Ballylosky, Fanningſtown, Rath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cannon, Clogher, Clon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bryen, Ballynenanty, Greallagh, Garebally, Broffe, Ballygrenane, Ballyvolhane, Fearan-Henry roe, Ballyſal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>laugh, Ballyvettoge, Ballyncolly, Cnockſaw<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ney, Clonygerra, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lenanemore, Ballyher<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rone, Clonmore, Rath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>marckey, Thomas town, Cahiraſſy.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kenry.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballyniſhane, Pallice, Ballydowell, Ballyva<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nane, Killeſaragh, Dro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>more, Ballyonollane, Keillmoreene, Caher Inereagh, Corry, Tuogh, Ballymickleharnane, Keilvarigie, Corry, Corry, Kiellknockane, Ballyvadane, Criggina<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cree, Ballyaſſea, Court mac Rynoll, Ballyoga<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>haſſy, Ballymacſhane<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>boy, Graigeaniſter, An<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lands town, Ballingady, Ballygadybeg, Ballin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>willen, Ballinahowe, Garryduffe, Gartannon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>teene, Gortenure, Mone<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>grany, Gortavilly, Kearhew, Garuffe, Li<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſancarry,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="34" facs="tcp:136892:20"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kildare, Went<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth Earl</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Clare and Lymerick. Galway and Limerick. Kilkenny.</p>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                        <p>Weſtmeath.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Ferancuddelly, Ballenfollardy, Ball<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>woodane, Parkmore, Ballygoſſy, &amp;c.</p>
                        <p>Kilcaſhin.</p>
                        <p>Kilcarnell <hi>alias</hi> Kilcar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>well.</p>
                        <p>Kerdons houſe in the City.</p>
                        <p>Sherlockſton, ſeveral houſes and lands in the town of Naas, Walter<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſton, Moynooth, New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Kelliſtown, Creffstown, Curretown, Collinſland, Newton<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>weſt <hi>al.</hi> Macabe, the Mannor of Kilka, great and little Bealand, Nar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>roghbeg, Rathculvin, Hubberſtown, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>naſe, little Birtown, Mullaghinaſte, Kilmead, Ballycollane, Ballyhyde, Ballynibarny, Youngs<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Ardnegreſſe, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lynybarney, the Man<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nor of Kildare, Browns<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Iriſhtown, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nure, Kilnabooly, Ardſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>coll, Donede, Philips<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Caſtleridy.</p>
                        <p>Keyle, Ballymullen Ali<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>as Milton, Pallagh Alias the Pace, Garrygevil and the Spittle houſe, the Mannor of Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>linderry <hi>alias</hi> the Slaughtne Arts, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>negeale <hi>alias</hi> Iriſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>towne, Ballynemacher, Leskevin, Machercoirk, Roskeay, Impire, Col<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rownig, Kilnevan, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lynobbane, Noghowal Portloman, Deſert alias Rathnobagdagh, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lynegallogath, Varvel<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtowne</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="35" facs="tcp:136892:20"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kildare, Went<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth Earl of</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Kerry and Deſmond.</p>
                        <p>Roſcom<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mon.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Garron. A ware on the River of Eniſh, <hi>alias</hi> Cartomugarrowe, Ballintogher, Coolam<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ber, Lockelſtown, Far<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rinmurry Ballynhiska<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nagh, Ballydronan, Ard<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>maghcar, Killeagh, Fer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ruffennagh, Barbrackan, the little Ruske, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neregan, Twoerane, Aghtybore, Brackagh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nehuly, Belane lower Ballyneran, Coolymne, Cleglaſs, Ballynebrye, Carneclonemacke, Clo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neregroy, Scarpe. The fiſhings on the Logh-Royal and the River of the ſame, a Caſtle near the ſame, Brennybegg, Ballyſallagh, Ballintlew, Ballintornan, Bancor, Knockunuit, Sarsfields<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Sydan, Mottown, Robbinſton, Caſtle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Kennaleagh, Mil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton, Newcaſtle, Caſtle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>corre, Rathbeg, Rath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>more, Moggilty, Clon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>colman, ſeveral Lands held by the Scept of Menter Brenan, the Countrey of Calry, Tooballynelly, the Countrey of Breawni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ury, the Country of Towennany, Ballymick<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nema, Biſhopſtown, Glaskrine, Rathaſpike, Kiltobber, Clonguillan, Keylnere and Cloncul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lan.</p>
                        <p>The fiſhings on the Ri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ver of Goolin and Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lycarbry.</p>
                        <p>Conymore, Cloneſalli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>aghe, Beahaghe <hi>al.</hi> Bea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ghe and Ballinegarragh.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="36" facs="tcp:136892:21"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kildare, Went<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth Earl</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Corke.</p>
                        <p>Galway.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Ballygorgan, Ballyne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>melagh, Caſtlemore. Biſſegnie, Ballaghe, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lyclanwilliamboy, Gort<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>netarnoge, Ballagh, Liſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nigriſie, The Rectory of Lickmataſh, Garry<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>duffe, Kilboggie, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rowemore, Ballyva<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rowghter, Kilmyoode, Templenan, Trymo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tume, Lowghnaton, Gurtenelaghen, Liſne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>grough, Liſſertary, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tragh, Leneghton, Clo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nefia, Carrynarke, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>crine, Leggen, Lonegh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton, Kilkrine, Carrow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nakitoe, Cograne.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Longford.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cartonacetapana, Mul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lagh, Liſſidaganie, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>logs, Seſſeveg, Liſna<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kaſhie, Dunleo, Clone<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lehane, Cartrona, Har<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>duarna, Killeronie, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rownikin, Rokan, Liſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>danille, Bitervaſe, Clon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nanayneneva, Stenagith, Irkare <hi>al.</hi> Toberntawry, Tobernikerhin, Low<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ghanamroge, Gortka<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>erne, Dowler, Carrown<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>meanagh, Truſcan, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rowgar, Lena, Renagh, Gurtin, Creran, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rowneanagh, Care<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mare, Clogh, Clonkin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>begg, Coolenearnock, lands in the town of Clare, Liſſenefranke, Clonnanynen, Truſtran <hi>al.</hi> Derrymane, Carrow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>keile, Carrownfeire, Longford, Greygane<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bony, Gregangarrowe, Tryanreanghe, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rownkilly, Aghrane, Dowlagh &amp; Naghrough,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="37" facs="tcp:136892:21"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kildare, Went<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth Earl</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Tipperary.</p>
                        <p>Wexford.</p>
                        <p>Wicklow</p>
                        <p>Mayo</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>the Rectories of Aſſu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fraigh <hi>al.</hi> Aſaskreagh and Kilſalen <hi>al.</hi> Killoſa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>len, and Liſſecharra, Rathmore, Rathne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gleny.</p>
                        <p>Garryhucke <hi>al.</hi> Jack-garden, Ballybeg, Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>maſton, Ballykellca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ghan <hi>al.</hi> Ballyclecaghan. Toomenyfanſhoge, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lyduffny, Killmare, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lyhamuck <hi>al.</hi> Kilma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nock, Garyvarowne, Caryhenigon, Gary<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>howe, Lackandarragh and Mone Edmond. Ballykeene <hi>al.</hi> Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>keine, Knockanemohill, Ballenepark and Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lenefunſhoge.</p>
                        <p>Glancoagh, Ballyvonell and Carrowkiltrone.</p>
                        <p>The penny place, and ſeveral houſes and lands in Dunboyne, Clony, Bennetſton, Rathtig, Hilton, Mounckton.</p>
                        <p>Several houſes and Lands in the Town of Duleeke, other parcels, viz. Maryridge, Mary<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land and Roodland, one Dove houſe and lands in Kinawde, Bretunſton, Broynanſton, Arrath &amp; Grenock, Newton of Moyaghy, Kildalkey, Knockodder, Top<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pſland, ſeveral houſes and Lands in the Town of Kells, Coocorr, Jen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kinſtown, Quoynſtown, Donoghſtown, Wood<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cockſtown, Warren<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtone, Barretſtowne, Wernockſtown, Gugh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>terhillagh, Cullentragh, The mannor of Rath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>skeagh,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="38" facs="tcp:136892:22"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kildare, Went<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth Earl of</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Kings.</cell>
                     <cell>Drumgoyle, &amp;c. Ballyſhane, Clonbrona, Ballynerve, Balline<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kelly, Clonecreane, Bo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lynarge, the Mannor of Egliſh, Derrynlogh, Ballyquillan, Cullani<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nore, Cullanvolly, the Iſland of Kiltobber, Ballinglaſſe <hi>al.</hi> Clonde<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>glaſſe, Kilvoyler, Leagh, Ballintrohan, Cullan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>beg, Cullanmore, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>connocke, Kilvem, Cur<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>raghroddery, Roſcurra <hi>al.</hi> Kneebeg, Killmoy<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lar, Gniew, Coſſan, Ilandwile, Knockbane, Tulchanmore, the Freagh, Clondelue, Streamſtown, Lands in Delny a mac Coghlan, Cameſhbegg, Ballykill mac Roſſny, Moyſtine, Ballinkillin, Doubran<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cher, Moylmich, Isker<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>caſtle, Killtauragh, Noybagh, Aghny, Droyne, Kilmunynog, Carramore <hi>al.</hi> the great Quart and Aghlena, Bancorr <hi>al.</hi> Bannagher with the fiſhing Ware, Caſtle and town there, Moyſlin, the Caſtle of Kilnegorrhenagh, Cow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>er, Caſtle Feddan, Ruſſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nis, Nabagh, Carrow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhinagh, Ballydona, Williamſton, Balleveri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>van, Ballintulchan, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>linanagh, Ballinkillin, Tullagh, Morahin, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lymore, Ballycony, Bal<g ref="char:EOLunhyphen"/>lykillmurey, Agbarny, Ballydroid, Caſtlebrack and the Country of Tooſmeare <hi>alias'</hi> Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>caſhany, Urike, Mony<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>coyle,</cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="39" facs="tcp:136892:22"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kildare, Went<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth Earl</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Cappaghilowcan, the great &amp; little park, Coolenepiſh, Carry<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>more, Clonveclahan, Culboran, Lawagh, Ruſcaghbeg, Arteblany, Moyhanagh, Bally mac Gilly, Sylan, Killmur<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rey, Ballynebracke, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tron mac Killy, Rath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>light, Killmore, Gad<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>danſtown and other lands in Ely, Carrol, the Mannor of Lea, &amp;c. Rathdonvoy, Boly<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bracke, Cogſhnohovan, Curra, and other lands, &amp;c. Garrinelegan, Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ghernehagh, Gartene<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gowen, with divers Wares on the River of Shannon, Maynes. Der<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rinioghe, Derrynagh, Garvally, Aghtene, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lenegarvaghe, Glen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cromine, Ardehorme, Moyſhlin, Killawragh, Moylagh, Aghie, <hi>alias</hi> Athie, Killmanyvoke, The Rahin, a yearly rent out of Sir John Mac Coghlans lands, Lanvaghe, Moynaghie and the pariſh thereof, Towmoyane, killniller, Ballni vohane, Kilmoy<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lecke, Killiene, Inchla<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cour, Derrnilaghe, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lynafalla, Ballykeale, Ballykillkallama, Litter, Loughan, Maghernore, Gortmelougha, Gurte<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>melee, Gurteneffees, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lenemore, Bally macder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mot, Cowldrie, Ballyk<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nochan, Bally mac murghe, Cappabirne, Roſſemore and Killma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>caddawe.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="40" facs="tcp:136892:23"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kildare, Went<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth Earl</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Longford</p>
                        <p>Queens Sligo.</p>
                        <p>Downe.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ballycowen.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Lynally, <hi>alias</hi> Sanvach, and Moyraghie.</p>
                        <p>Camagh, Correynagh, Smeare, Rathmore, Gukinroe, Taugaght, Breaghwoy, Sunnagh, Camroayne, Cullough, Barry, Deſertdolagh, Leſlight, Ballynaght and Ralight.</p>
                        <p>The Strate Diſhoke. Carrowdrom, Cor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>micke, Carrowomigan, Carrowcarrymilton, Carrowgranymore, Carrownecrene, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>roweliſdowgan, Clane<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gaſhel, Lands in the Territory of Slaight.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ofliny.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Shaneboy Mac Owen Hara; Cowlecaſhell, Cornmick, Leighcar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rowdullogh, and Leighcarrowknappard, the Caſtle Lordſhip and Land of Slygo, Tire<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>connel, Kilnisky, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bery, Fermanacke with ſeveral other parcels in Connaught, Clonmur<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rey, Cornetrig, Roſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>crib, Wranck, Carrow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ougin, Carrowe, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rimiltin, Carrowgru<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nem, ſeveral parcells of Land in or near Cowle and Caſhell, Cormicke, Leighcarrowe, Tallagh, Leighcarrowknappe, The Rectories of Aſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſaghfragh, <hi>alias</hi> Agha<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>skragh, Kilſalen, <hi>alias</hi> Killoſlen, &amp;c.</p>
                        <p>The cuſtomes, &amp;c. of Ardglaſs, Strangford, Killogh, Shipland, Por<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>taferry and all other the</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="41" facs="tcp:136892:23"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Kildare, Went<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth Earl of</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                        <p>Wexford &amp; Wicklow</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Forts and Creeks on the River of Strang<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ford and Loghquanie, Corballyes, Ballyregan. Pryorſtowne, Knocke and Callaghcurry.</p>
                        <p>Both the Annaghs and Ballinward, Pallis A<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chulline, Mawghor, the Mannor of old Roſſe, <hi>viz.</hi> Ballyboly, Killskan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lan, Rocheſtown, Balli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>melagh and Breymli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>more, Newbane Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>naght, the Mannor of Killonghy, <hi>alias</hi> Kille<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gin, <hi>viz.</hi> Knockſtown, Freſhalſtou, Kingstown, Ballyſtraghboe. The Tomenerlies and the Quenlaght, &amp;c. Clon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>roch, Ballyvonin, To<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nyferny, Downany, the Roddenagh, Garrin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tanſey, Raturtin, the two Clondeliffs, the Great Forreſt, Bir<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neſtown, Rackardſtown, Ballyſhane, the mannor and Town of Dipps, <hi>viz.</hi> Ballyneſlany, Roſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſard, Ballybo and Caſtleton, &amp;c, Kilche<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>relagh, Ballyhobin, St. Michans Chappel and Roches Conycrew, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>corly, Adromminac<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>core, Powers mill and the Earls meadow, the Ferry of Roſſe, Ca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fisſtown, Preſtallſtown, Dowdwarfe, the Parſo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nage and Viccarage of Old Roſs, Naſh, Cul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>linſtown, Ballyshinan. The Stone houſe, Pier<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſtown, Ardmore, Ballyronum, Ken<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>leſtown, Ballyarnum,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="42" facs="tcp:136892:24"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Killegin, both Clon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dalies, Robſtown, Bryneſtown, Woolfer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtown, Caſtlenech, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lygormogan, Roche<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtown, Rodiſton, <hi>alias</hi> Brymilemore, <hi>alias</hi> Kilſtalan, and Ballyne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>boly, Ballyſhenan, the Government, &amp;c. of Roſs, all the land in Faſſagh of Bentry, the mills of old Roſs and Roſſeponter, the Iſland of Dromduffe, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>brittas, Minemore, Garrynarren, Killaco<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vat, Ballyot, Ballymer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gin, Ballyhenecke and Ballynekerd.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Lutterell Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Six houſes in the Pre<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cinct of S. John with<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>out Newgate.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleknock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Lutterels town, Bran<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>doingrove, Killiſtor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nane, Balleſtrowen <hi>alias</hi> Stravanſtown, Skirmul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lin, Clanſillagh, James<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land, Finnighſland, Bar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>biſtown, Kiſſianſtown, Coninſtown, Frebleck<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton, Barnegeath, great Stahenny.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Godamendy, Miſſels<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Huntſtown, the Pace, Whites-town, Diſwellſtown, Carpen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ters-town, Blanchers<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Scaltweod <hi>alias</hi> Greatwood.</p>
                        <p>Ballyowen, Esker, Fid<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>danſtown, Biſhopsfield, Loughtown, Rathcoole, Colemanſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Lucan, Ballydowde, Baldonan, Flockmea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dowe,</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Kildare</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Naas.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The Naas, Phinceſton, Rathsker.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Salt.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Lexly, Toberſhoghlin, Danamore, Fleſſesſtown, Muchrath, Lanckton.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Clare.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Abbey of Clare, New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dunboyne.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballymacolly, Maſtock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſton, Hawkinſton, Roes<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Walterſtown, Rathleeke, Dunboyne, Loghſallagh, Mileſtown, Curtlaghſton, Bennett<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſton, Kilbrenan, Mayne, Gunnogs, Handcocks<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land, Osburnſland.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ratooth.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Fearnehouſe, and other houſes and lands.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Deece.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Toubly part.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleeke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Finnor, Mooretown, Rowleſtown, Millhill, Clowneſtown.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="43" facs="tcp:136892:24"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Coldcott, Fryer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Killakee, Stayony.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>
                              <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>ppercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Rahincullagh, Killima<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>talway, Bruine <hi>al.</hi> Bo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>herbrane.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nethercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Killeagh, Tibberbir, Cotterelſtown, the Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctory of Durabate.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleknock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Voltanſtown, Lawrence<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Owens town, Clunſillagh.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrothery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Knockroder.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Leynes Bartho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lomew, &amp; Eli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nor <hi>
                           <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>x.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Three houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nethercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Swords.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrodery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Grallagh.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nethercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Littlebealingſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Coolecolt, Crumlyn and New Mill.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nethercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballhary.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                        <p>Meath Lowth</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Salt.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Lexlip. Miniſtown.</p>
                        <p>Several Tenements.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Luttrell Alice, <hi>al.</hi> S. Lawrence Widdow.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>A houſe in High-ſtreet, another houſe.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleknock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Duſwelſtown, Bland<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cherdſton, Schallwood, Blackethmil, Lucan, Rathcole. <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi> Killmatalvey, Frierton, Coſſerelſton, Cloghro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>der, Cotterelſtown, Killakee, Slagony.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtle Carbery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballyonan, Ballinekilly.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Kildare</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Naas.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Rahesker, Naas.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Clane.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Clane.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Salt.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Donamore, Lexlip.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dunboyne.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Dunboyne, Mayne, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>brenan, Handcockland.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleeke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Rowleſton, Morton.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Screene.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Clowneſton.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Moor Patrick</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Martin Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe, cellar and garden in the Wood<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>key.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="44" facs="tcp:136892:25"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Martin Willi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>am</cell>
                     <cell>One tenement in Caſtle-ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Minſhal Sir Richard and Dame Mary <hi>Vx</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Eight houſes, 19 Meſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſuages.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrudery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Kilcrogh, Jordans town, Cotterelſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nethercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Regliſh of Luske with the tithes thereof.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Longford</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ardagh.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cullenny, Serieagh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>morefada, Kriaghadoe, Kriewiny, Homane, Corribane, Culmahenſy, Liſnamucky, Garnuke<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſagh, Cnockachahud, Glacke, Clenragh, Doonenamalagh, Fie<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>aghfada.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Mallone Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Fourty three houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleknock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Kilmaineham, Polemill, Phepeſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Weſtpanſtown, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>doude.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nethereroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The third part of the great tithes of Gry<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nocke, Kilſalchan and Chappel-midway, Brownſtown, Culdrie.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coll ck.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Dunbro.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Turimore.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Meath.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Skreene.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Liſmull in with the great and ſmall tithes, Jurdanſtown, Blandes<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Loughtown, Caſtletown.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Mey Matthew</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Seven houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Athgoe, Newcaſtle, Kilmatalway, Kilmain<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ham.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Meath.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ratouth.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ratouth.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Milles Ralph Orphan</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Eight houſes &amp;c.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Moyles Caſtle, Black<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>borns land, Wards land <hi>alias</hi> Korkagh Farme.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Murtagh Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Maſon Mat<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thew &amp; Elinor <hi>
                           <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>x.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>One plot of ground and one houſe.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="45" facs="tcp:136892:25"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Meath Henry, Lord Biſhop</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Six Parks or Cloſes, Ballyboughte, S. James Pariſh.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coolock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballybought, Driſhoge, Drumconragh, Clyn<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mell, Glaſnevyne, Sta<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>coole, Ballygriffin.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrotherie.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Baltra, &amp;c. Balcarrid.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Eaſtmeath.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleek.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Athcarne, Deens, Clony, Dollerſtown, Hayeſtown, Great Boolies, little Boolies, Knock Iſland, Micknanſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Skreene.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballrath, Ardmullcan, Johnſtown, Rathfeagh, Slaneſtown, Ediketown, Great Waterſide, Little Waterſide, Iriſhtown, Timole.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Morgallen.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Shilliogge, Wilkins<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Nottingham Ignatius</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Nottingham Peter</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Five houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballyowen, Ealker, Lu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>can, Nanger, Ballydoud, Clandolkan, Killmar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tin, Fininſtown, Poores<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Kildare.</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Athgarred, Little New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Kildrathad. Partmany, Pinkins.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Plunket Chri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtopher</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Two houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Rathdown.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>James land, Pluncketts parks.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balruddery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Chief rent of Tankards town, Rent of Wax out of little Ballagheragh.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Navan.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Prieſtrath, Five tene<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ments.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ratouth.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>One tenement, little Dorix, Racroſſane, two tenements in Crenock, with ten acres of land.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Plunckett Thomas</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Two houſes, two gar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dens, one Orchard, and one park, in S. Katha<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rines pariſh, one houſe and a Backſide in S. Ni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cholas Pariſh without the Walls, two tene<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ments, one Garden, and one Orchard, <hi>idem.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>In Brownſtown 160 acres, Barrony of Ne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thercroſs and Balrothe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rie.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Louth</cell>
                     <cell>Bewly, Blakeſtown and Ballinreske, New town, Barſplunckett, ſixty acres in Jermin Fearn, twenty acres in Balray, Laraghmenſhy, Balma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>glan, ſixty acres in Pri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ors town, twenty acres in Miltown, ſixty acres in Galcowes town. Pipers town, Cottrels<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, ninety acres in Browns town, five acres</cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="46" facs="tcp:136892:26"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Meath Droghedah</cell>
                     <cell>and a Milne in Kercock, Three acres &amp; an houſe in Rathdrumner, fourty acres in Nichols town, ſixty acres in Dunleere, fifteen acres in Burrin, thirty acres in Rahaſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>car, thirty acres in Swineſtown, ninety acres in Peoganſtown, thirty acres in Finway. Sixty acres in Gronfty. In the town of Droghe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dah, two houſes in Weſt-ſtreet on old walls and garden in the North ſide of the ſaid ſtreet, one park of two acres, one houſe in Batchelors lane, 2 parks in Green<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bater, two parks and a Milne without S. Sun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>days gate, two parks in Yellow-bater, a park neer the Green hills, one tenement in S. Laurence ſtreet, Fyans Roe.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Pilkinton Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas, Alice <hi>Vx.</hi> and Wakefield John</cell>
                     <cell>Three houſes.</cell>
                     <cell>Wexford.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Gory.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Killibeggs.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Payne Joſeph</cell>
                     <cell>Two Tenements.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Penteny Ri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chard</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>One houſe in Oxman<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrodery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Knock-Tirkinton, Boe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hill.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coolock</hi> and <hi>Nethercroſs.</hi> Surgoſtown, Laresſtown, Croſshouth.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Percivall Sir <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 word">
                           <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>One meſſuage in S. Ni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cholas ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="47" facs="tcp:136892:26"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Pluncket Sir Nicolas and Dame Kathe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rine and others</cell>
                     <cell>The corner houſe in Winetavern ſtreet in M. Palfreys poſſeſſion, houſes, one cellar, one Horſe-mill.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Wexford.</p>
                        <p>Wicklow</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>63 Meſſuages, gardens and tofts, the Caſtlehill, Fagh and S. Johns, Buldlort, Tynnicarry, Tynniknock, Rathne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mony, Ballirahine. Anarelly, Ballenetunny, Balleneskeagh with the tythes, Balleneparky, Balleſallagh.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Purcel William and Edmond.</cell>
                     <cell>3 Houſes.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Pierce Dame Elinor</cell>
                     <cell>One Cloſe.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Plunkett Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>One houſe.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coolock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Bagatrath, Portmar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nock, Carrickhill.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Mayo</cell>
                     <cell>Ballanidoe, Dowmore, Carrownelegan, Knock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neaghan, Rathbane, Knockgrany, Iverland, Cowbegg, Cowla.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Plunkett An<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gell and Fran<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cis Plunkett</cell>
                     <cell>Twenty ſix houſes.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Lune.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Rathmore, Ballinto<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gher, Ballivanan, Gar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ranban, Rathconny, Derriconer, both the Clownies, both the Gills towns, Lincher<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land, Moyagher part.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kells.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Fords town, Ballagh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>boy, Dowrath, New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Corraghtown, Ruoriſtown, Scurlocks<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>S. Patricks the Dean and Cha<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pter.</cell>
                     <cell>The Chantry lands of S. Annes, The tythes of great and little Ca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bragh.</cell>
                     <cell>Wicklow</cell>
                     <cell>Rathmuck, Ballyogan, and Rathſalcan, the tithes of Aſhtown, and Pelſtown.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Palſrey Ri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chard</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Four houſes and a Ten<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nis Court.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrothery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Newinnings in Reynolds town.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Pain John Eſq;</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="48" facs="tcp:136892:27"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>S. Patricks Vi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cars Chorals Corporation</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Plunkett Chri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtopher</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>One Meſſuage in Cook<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet.</p>
                        <p>Dunſoughly, Harris<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Brachan, New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town of Dunſoughly, S. Margery Dubbore, Uttermoye, Joneſtown, Merifall, Balleskin, Kill<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>donan, Cillmacmonan, Hallowood, Rath, Don<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nabate, Cromlin, Mill-Dawiſpark, Luske, Knock, Balrodry, Tanchardſtown.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>Loghgoure, little Logh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>goure, Morton, Molli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nan, Ballimore, Ponder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lagh, Colleſtown, Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kinſtown, Rathbegan, Warringſtown, Partans, Dunſalin, Gallmore-Iſland in Rathtouth, Preiſtrath, ſeveral houſes in Rathtouth, Flemmington, Runtons<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Moyaghery, Cur<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>raghtown, Kells, Mol<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lagheh, Gonnox, Mag<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ginſyard, Greens park, Finglas Bridge.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Plunkett Ri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chard</cell>
                     <cell>One tenement in S. James ſtreet, one houſe in S. Thomas ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kells.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Croſſe Kille.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Plunkett Wal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes in the City and Suburbs, late belonging to Thomas Plunkett Alderman.</cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Deece.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Dirpatrike, Littletown, Mullaughine, Tullagh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>medan, Augher Turin and the Barons Farm, Knockmark, Allens land, Bedfaſtown, Dromry, Plunketts land, the Colledge houſes and lands, Moor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Talbote, the Glane, Killtale and Branganſtown.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Palles James and Mary</cell>
                     <cell>Two houſes in Corn<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>market, two houſes in High-ſtreet, one houſe in Back lane, one houſe in S. Frances ſtreet, 3 l. <hi>per an.</hi> out of three parks and one Orchard in New-ſtreet, 20 l. <hi>per an.</hi> on Dunſoghly, New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton and Bragon, 15 l. out of and 150 l. mort<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gage</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Lowth</p>
                        <p>Meath.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Alexander.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>20 l. <hi>per an.</hi> out of Ard<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vally, 200 l. Mortgage on Caſtletown, 50 l. mortgage on Cooks<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, 160 l. mortgage on Alexander Reads land.</p>
                        <p>8 l. <hi>per ann.</hi> out of Har<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>locks town, a ſtatute ſtaple of 600 l.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="49" facs="tcp:136892:27"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>on Kildonane and Balliskin, Talbots Farm in Crumlin, 26 l. mort<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gage out of Rochords Farm in Crumlin, a ſta<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tute ſtaple of 200 l.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>80 l. <hi>per an.</hi> out of Cri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vitenall.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Quinn Peter</cell>
                     <cell>3 Houſes, 3 ſhops, &amp;c. Cluntarfe.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath.</p>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Deece.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Agherske, Tury, Bed<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>faſtown, Mooretown, Feneſland, Knockmark, Kilcoolie.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Soneboyne.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Saleſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleeke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Dardeſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Clane.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Longetown.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Quatrod Ni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cholas</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Oxmon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Quinne John</cell>
                     <cell>4 Houſes, &amp;c. and a Gar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>den, Clonſlagh and cer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tain houſes, &amp;c.</cell>
                     <cell>Wexford.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Forth.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Garriſynott, Kildeiske, Talbottſtown, Heares<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mead, Collenſtown.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Quinne Marcus</cell>
                     <cell>Nine houſes.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Roſcommon, Wentworth Earl</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Roſcommon houſe in Oxmantown.</p>
                        <p>Several houſes lands and tenements.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Trim, Navan, Kells.</hi> Athlone, Athboy.</p>
                        <p>In Blagh ſtreet.</p>
                        <p>The tenements in poſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſeſſion of Robert Rate<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gam, Widow Lloyd, Robert Ferral, James Nutter, John Hopkins, Patrick Helane, John Griffin, George Dob<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſon, Garrat Barry, Pa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>trick Helane and George Dobſon.</p>
                        <p>In Market-ſtreet.</p>
                        <p>Iſaac Reynolds, Walter Walſh, Widow Willi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ams, Alexander Jepth<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſon, Tho. Graunt, Tho. Weſt, John Hopkins.</p>
                        <p>In High-ſtreet.</p>
                        <p>William May, William</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="50" facs="tcp:136892:28"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Roſcommon Wentworth Earl</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Harriſon, Mrs. Newman, Tho. Kelly, Richard Helane, Moragh, Logh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>len, Richard Clowde, Derby Fine, Teige Fo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ranane, John Hely, Da<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vid Bourke, Thade Dil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lon, Mrs. Brinnin, Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bert Quely, Paul Ne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lane, William Mallore, Tho. Taylor, and Chri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtopher Kernons.</p>
                        <p>In Blynd-ſtreet.</p>
                        <p>Paul Nelane, Thady Dillon, Chriſtopher Kernan, James Kernan, and Owen Brinnans.</p>
                        <p>In Haggard-ſtreet. Joſeph Preſsick and Mallone, John Rely, Nicholas Sheely, Do<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nogh Foronan, Charls Connor, three gardens nigh the Church, Mo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rogh, Loghlin, 2 parks without Nauan-gate, 1 near the great Mill, 1 other without Blagh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gate called Hoppyard, Patrick Chaine, John Martin, a fiſhing Weire over againſt the Maud<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lins and Dirby, Lide<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ocks.</p>
                        <p>In the Navan.</p>
                        <p>In Horſend-ſtreet two tenements in the hands of one Jacob, one near the wall in the Bakers occupation, one other poſſeſſed by a Cooper near Trym gate one o<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther by Graham, Wa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fers caſtle, alſo a Cab<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bin, and a garden there.</p>
                        <p>In <hi>Kells.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>In S. Johns ſtreet one tenement, in Maudlins ſtreet one tenement</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="51" facs="tcp:136892:28"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Roſcommon Wentworth Earl</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Eaſtmeath.</p>
                        <p>Weſtmeath.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>with two gardens, in Carrigſtreet one waſte tenement.</p>
                        <p>In <hi>Athlone</hi> in Iriſhtown Nine tenements.</p>
                        <p>In <hi>Athboy</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ten tenements.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Navan.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Newtown, Ardgreagh, Rathnally and the mill, Harbertſtown, Dungen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ny, Mogomet, Clunfane, Vallenaughton, Felles<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Cloundavan, Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>binrath.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Deece.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Grange, Creroge, little Finglogh town.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Moyfenragh.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Foſters town, Earbers<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Turnie, Mawd<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lins, the Mill of New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Lune.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Woodtown-abbot, Fil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pots town <hi>al.</hi> Moneſhal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>labod, Dervor, Rath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>carran.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Halfowre.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Dyamore, Martinſtown, Thomas town, Willi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ams town, Phillips town, Patricks town <hi>al.</hi> Partridg town, Ballni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vally, Knocklogh, Ken<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>naghan.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Rathconrath.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Shonliſh, Beologh and Agloghbane.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kilkenny</hi> weſt.</p>
                        <p>Cluonkeene, Cloghir, Creggah; Ballynenoan, Gnivenemanagh, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kenny, Ferraneskehie, Liſnesrkiny &amp; Tullagh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>anglaſs, Knocknegonin, the Plow land of the caſtle of Walterſtown, Rathbreack, Ballintro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hane, the Iſland of In<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>niſhbofin,</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="52" facs="tcp:136892:29"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Longford</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>the tithes of Kilkenny, Bryanmor, the Abby of Athlone, Spit<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tlehouſe and tenements called Garragh, Cluo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ninore and Middowe.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Cluonlonun.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Boyledonnogh, Hories, Boyanagh, Tyrodono<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lon, Black Hories, Knockſhane <hi>al.</hi> Graunts land 20 acres.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Rathconrath.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Garragh, Cluonagh, Shyeg, Liſnegrio, Fer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ranegawne, Belanimo, Athboy, Buolegaroc<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kan, Feranekirk, the Caſtle Cartron, Crag<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gan, Aghaconner, Agha<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>temple, Boleredmond, Mount Cornely, Ardne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gacone, Garrowe, Sca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hardand, Cappudna, Farribregge, Atteniu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>roona, Carrowreagh, Cluonibreene.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Shrule.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Keele, Carrigge, Rath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>begg, Rathmore, Tange, Newcaſtle, Garrincorr <hi>al.</hi> Corr, Abby of Shrule, Cloghanbedy, Aghanderry, Tullonon, Cluonſuſe, Townſted, The Fairs, fiſhings, Wares and mills, Clu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>onebreen, Drumliſne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gereagh, Dromanure, Rathorne, Killree, Rath<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſallowe, Killinboy, Cnockagh, Ballynema<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nagh, Liſnecreave, and Cronagh, Forgney, A<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>crecam, Tomerick, Cla<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rinullagh, Tonag<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>knock, Ballycor, Aghni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dramen.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="53" facs="tcp:136892:29"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Longford</p>
                        <p>Tipperary</p>
                        <p>Kings.</p>
                        <p>Cavan.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Shrule.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Agnehend, Aghnagan, Corbane, Leter, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>macknemae.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Rathline.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Moegh, Caſtlecor, De<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>roge, Knockboy.</p>
                        <p>Cluoneen, Grange, Gortnevulny, Mona<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſterg, Litterluna and Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctory, Cluoncreken. 54 Acres in Ballyvinaſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſedy, Roſcullinagh, and Droninicam, the moun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tain of Shevobloome, Mucklone, the Vica<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rages of Kilcoman, and Aghencon, the Rectory of Syrakeran, Linnet, Littere, Roſcowragh, Inchinebeo, Corbally, Cluonirekeen, Cowly<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhell, Killcoleman, Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lenokennet, Balleca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſlane, Ardare, Garry<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hand, Ballybrit, Mony<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fadda, Lenybanan. Moonery one pole of land with appurtenan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ces, alſo ſeveral Fairs and markets in the Counties of Weſt<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>meath, Kings, Mayo, Gal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>way, Sleygo, and Roſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>common.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Ruſſel Chri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtopher</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p n="16">16. Houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nethereroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Seatowne, Newtowne, <hi>alias</hi> Knockmowles, Kelleys farm, 20 houſes and a great ſtonewall, Gammwell, Smythes<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land, the Firr park, Tampanfield.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Rellick George.</cell>
                     <cell>2 Houſes.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="54" facs="tcp:136892:30"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Relly Stephen.</cell>
                     <cell>2 Tenements, &amp;c. Mary acre.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Rogerſon Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Read Bigget.</cell>
                     <cell>Two houſes.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Roe Henry and Ellinor <hi>
                           <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>x.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Several ſtatutes upon ſeveral perſons in the City of <hi>Dublin.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Rery Fitz Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bert</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>A houſe in Thomas Street.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleknock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Colletrath, Sprickles<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Gallantſton, Cor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>reſtown, Chappell-Midway.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ratooth.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Grenog.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Strong James, Richard and Chriſtopher</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Five houſes.</p>
                        <p>The Rectory and tithes of Sherlockſtown, a Statute ſtaple againſt Chriſtopher and Henry Burnell late of Caſtle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>knock, and Edmond Geaſhell of Paſlocks<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Sedgrave Law<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rence.</cell>
                     <cell>The third part of the Precinct Ambite of St. John the Baptiſt.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Sheet James Dr.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Saltonſtal Samuel.</cell>
                     <cell>A houſe in Corne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>market.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>John Sergeant.</cell>
                     <cell>A houſe in High-ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Sarsfield Pa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>trick.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>2 Houſes, a mill and a parke.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Lucan, Waſpanstown, Padingstown, great and little Bolinetagh, Al<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lenswood and Sagard.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Kildare.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Offaly.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Tully, Braiistown, Fry<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>erstown, Merny, Mar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tinstown, Kilbrid, Loughbroan, ſeveral Tenements in Kildare, Rathbryde, the tythes</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="55" facs="tcp:136892:30"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>
                              <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>ppercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Rathcoole.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Wicklow</p>
                        <p>Kings.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>and Rectories of Fry<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ers town, Rathbryde, Kilcorkry, Davids town, Duneny, Ballygreny, Rathmuke, Fenner, Ballihinoge and Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>necailagh.</p>
                        <p>Old <hi>Connel.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Roſeberry, and Clun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gorie, Corvells, Cor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vells Court, Scarlets<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Ricards town, Clungaunagh. The Tythes and Rectories of Mooretown, Roſeberry, and Killelan.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Kilcullen.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The tythes and Recto<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ries of Thomas town, and Mooretown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Maraghandreban.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The tythes and Recto<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ries of Lipstown, Blake<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hall and Calverstown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Naaſe.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Turnings, Clunings, Killinemore, White-Church, Ladycaſtle, Stone mill and Barron<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rath.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Clane.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballynecapoke, Bea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>taughtowne, Maud<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>leeves and Clane.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Shillelly.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>The Rectories of Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>now, Hackets town and Gilberstown.</p>
                        <p>The tythes of Raghan, Lynoll, Killaghy, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hin, Ballyhoy, Drum<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cullen, Egliſh, Kilbrid and Kilmurry, <hi>alias</hi> Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>manchan and the Parſo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nage of Killurim.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Seagrave John</cell>
                     <cell>3. Houſes in Highſtreet, one in Bridgſtreet, 3 in St. Nicholas-ſtreet, 3 in</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleeke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Bartons town, Bel<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lewſton &amp; Ballinegarvy.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="56" facs="tcp:136892:31"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>St. Francis-ſtreet, 1 Mault-houſe in Oxmon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mantown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nethercroſs,</hi> part of <hi>Newcaſtle,</hi> &amp; <hi>Vpper<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>croſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Collects Inn <hi>al.</hi> the old Exchequer and Higgin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>green, little Cabragh, Finglas wood, New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>grange, Kilmacredocke, and Ballykellmore, Muchmore and little Wayre.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrothery,</hi> and <hi>
                              <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>ppercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Tubergraigan, Gares<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Kilmakargin.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nethercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Colcot and Tuſſagart, Ballyboggan.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ratouth.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>A Statute ſtaple of 1200 l. on Rathbeggan.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Springham Thomas</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>A houſe in Bridg-ſtreet.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleknock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Killmenaham.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell rows="2">
                        <p>Taylor Mary, and Bridget</p>
                        <p>Talbot Willi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>am</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>One houſe.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Six houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Two waſte pieces of ground, Five tenements with 26 acres of land.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Louth</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dondalk.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Haggards town, New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Killalyn, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>balrick.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Tyreconnel Earl</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>A houſe, Merriyonny, Rings end, Baggots Rath.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>A houſe and plot of ground, Finſtown, Kil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tale.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Rathdown.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Caleragh.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleknock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cappuck.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Rathdowne.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Bullerſtown, Kilterna<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nin, Mallalride.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Wicklow</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Downe.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Rathdown.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Great Bray.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Navan.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Hallanſtown and Athro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nan.</p>
                        <p>Templeton, Moore<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town and Mucklough.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="57" facs="tcp:136892:31"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coolock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Symons Court, Owens<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Rathdown.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Dundrum, Glancullea, Little Bray, Killinacud.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Talbot Willi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>am</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Eight houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coolock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Puckſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balrothery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Balwinſtown, Edeſtown, Garriſtown.</p>
                        <p>The <hi>Croſſe.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Swords, Kahinny, Cor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ballis.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Caſtleknock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Stradwally, Clandalkin, Kilmainum.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Meath</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Ratooth.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Roberts town, Johns<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Donreagh, Little Bulſtown, Greenock.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Talbott Mar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gery</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Certain houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balreddery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Garriſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Nethercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Swords, Puckſtown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balruddery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballwynſtown, Dolphins Barne.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Taaffe, <hi>alias</hi> Cook Julian</cell>
                     <cell>Tyrenure.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Talbot Sir Henry</cell>
                     <cell>One waſte piece of ground without S. James gate, Madder garden, 8 Tenements in S. James, 1 Tenement in S. Thomas ſtreet, 18 Tenements in S. Francis ſtreet, 1 Tenement on the Corn market, 1 Te<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nement in S. Patrick-ſtreet, 6 Tenements in Sheep-ſtreet, the Brick<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>walls in Caſtle-ſtreet, 2 Tenements in Fiſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>amble-ſtreet, 6 Tene<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ments in Skinner Roe,</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="58" facs="tcp:136892:32"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>1 Tenement in S. Ni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cholas pariſh, the wine<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tavern gate with 6 Te<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nements, 1 Tenement in Wine-tavern ſtreet, 3 Tenements oppoſite the old Crane.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Uſher Arlenter</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Four houſes and a Ten<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nis Court.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Newcaſtle Vppercroſs.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cromlin, Clandalkin.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Valden Sil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>veſter</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Uſher George and Alice <hi>Vx.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Twenty five houſes.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coolock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Sutton, Whitſtown, Hayes town, the Rath, Baldangan.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Kildare</p>
                        <p>Roſscom<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mon Weſtmeath</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Moyfanragh.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Freefans <hi>al.</hi> little Free<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fans, Richardſtown, Hoartown.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleeke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Rath Cane, Trim.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Salt.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Calrow town and the tithes, Kill.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Roſscommon.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>A Mortgage of 200 l. Multerfarnan.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Uſher Arlenter of Cromlin.</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Fiſhamble ſtreet, one Orchard and Garden, one piece of waſte ground in Cook<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Uſher Henry</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>One Stone houſe.</p>
                        <p>The Mannor of Baldon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gan, Lytown, Ballens<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Whites town, Hayes town, the Rath.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Coolock.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Sutton and other lands.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Catherlagh</p>
                        <p>Wicklow</p>
                        <p>Weſtmeath</p>
                        <p>Meath.</p>
                        <p>Roſscom<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mon.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>The Rectory of Ar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tlo, &amp;c.</p>
                        <p>The parſonage of Kill<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>magorge.</p>
                        <p>The lands of the Abbey of Mullifarnan.</p>
                        <p>Beartanſtown and Bal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dongan.</p>
                        <p>Cloynreny, Sanvally Mac Corvill, Agdrum<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nagh, Caldragh, Liſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gilroe, Lyſhumuske, Gorſeloghan and Clonne.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="59" facs="tcp:136892:32"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Wiſeman Ed<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ward and Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ry <hi>
                           <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>x.</hi>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Caſtle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>White Domi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nick and Luke White.</cell>
                     <cell>Fourteen houſes, three ſhops, and certain par<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cels of ground.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Warren Peter and John War<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ren.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>A houſe in S. Kavans pariſh.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>County.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Danabrook, Corneſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>court, Glaunemucke, Ballowley.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>White Stephen</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>One houſe on the Wood-key, one waſte houſe in S. Francis<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Balruddery.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>10 l. <hi>per annum</hi> out of Little Hollywood.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Lowth</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dundalk.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>One Caſtle, 24 acres &amp; a half, and 10 houſes in Carlingford.</p>
                        <p>Seven houſes, one Orchard, and one Croft in Drogheda.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Arder.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Two houſes in Arder.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleeke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Fifty two acres in Har<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kinſton.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <hi>Additional</hi>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="60" facs="tcp:136892:33"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Banks Elinor</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in High<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Brown Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes in Dub<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lin, one Caſtle in Clon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dalkin, Seskin.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Ball <hi>al.</hi> Gough Ann</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Ram-Lane, the thirds of Bar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tholomew Balls eſtate.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Baggot Elinor &amp; al.</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes in Dub<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lin and Oxmantown, Clandalkin, Clown<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>burrus.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Downeſtown, Slane, the tythes of Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ferman.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Bamber Ri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chard</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes in Dub<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lin.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Brown Sir Ri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chard</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes in Dub<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lin.</cell>
                     <cell>Longford</cell>
                     <cell>Killmoore, Ballykenny, Tully Rowe, Bailyri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chan, Killeclogh, Cer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rillman, Drumderrick, Cullaghneddagh, Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chilboy, Carridmere, Tuma, Feaghmoore, Tarrybog, Corryglaſs, Liſſahanedan, the fiſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing Were of Ballybeg, Keebe, Clunart, Bo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hine, Clogher, Tully, Monteryelgan, Cnock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>angoly, Sin, Friaghnane, Carrylackluanagh, Car<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ryballentampan, Done<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gall, Knodoragh, Balle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>garne, Agheratna, Balle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>namoore, Caldragh, Gobedagh, Clonelegh, Clunellan, Risbage.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Barnwall Ri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chard</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Cook<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet Dublin, Liſpople, Drumnifield, Knock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bryne, Roganſtown.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath.</p>
                        <p>Louth.</p>
                        <p>Moneghan.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>With a Water-mill, S. Johns Rath, Staba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nan, Lychiſtown, other lands, Carlingford, Ballug, Corballies, Cowly, Balliregan, Brockaroagh.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Brook William and his wife</cell>
                     <cell>Several tenements on the Wood-key.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="61" facs="tcp:136892:33"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Bath Richard and others</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes in Dub<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lin and Oxmantown, Glaſnevin.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Monaghan</p>
                        <p>Meath.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Annaghagh, Dennis<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town.</p>
                        <p>Balgeeth.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Brown John of Neals town</cell>
                     <cell>Several houſes in Dub<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lin, Rowlagh, Steeple<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>farm, Cappaghs, Barnes<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>wood, Clandalkin, Nealſtown, Ballgaddy, Bally mac negine, Bally mac Kenny, Hoyles half farm, Clanborries, Parſ-Moores, Haumleſs half farm, Rathline, Skellinſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ford, a Watermill in Kings mills town.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Blackny Willi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>am</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Dublin. Reykentore, Sankers town, Balcunry, Heaths town, Nodds town, Wiſe town, Adams town, Freeland, Par<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kinſtown.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Carberry Ni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cholas</cell>
                     <cell>Several Meſſuages, &amp;c.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Clanbraſel Henry Earl</cell>
                     <cell>S. Maryes diſſolved Abbey, &amp;c.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Clarke George</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Stephen ſtreet, two houſes, gar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dens and Backſides in James ſtreet, three houſes, gardens and backſides in S. Thomas ſtreet, one houſe in the Backlane with a back<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſide, one houſe in S. Patrick ſtreet with a garden and backſide.</cell>
                     <cell>Kildare</cell>
                     <cell>Two hundred and fifty pounds due on John Clarkes eſtate, three hundred pounds due on James Euſtace his lands in Moone, in the right of his wife.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Crump Chri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtopher &amp; <hi>Vx.</hi> Robert Barn<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>well &amp; <hi>
                           <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>x.</hi> Lawrence Pur<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>field and Igna<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tius Hurſell</cell>
                     <cell>One Leaſe for 61 years by the Maſter and War<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dens of S. Anns Guild, an annuity of 10 l. <hi>per an.</hi> to iſſue out of a houſe in Cornmarket, one Bond of the ſtaple of</cell>
                     <cell>Kildare</cell>
                     <cell>Four Meſſuages, 67 a<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cres of land in Ardreſſe Barrony of Salt, one Annutty of 5 l. <hi>ſterl.</hi> out of Corners Court, one Annuity of 10 l. <hi>per an.</hi> out of Corners</cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="62" facs="tcp:136892:34"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>of 320 l. acknowledged by Patrick Halgan.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>court, a leaſe of 99 years out of Monally.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dowdal Igna<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tius</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Wine<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tavern ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell>Lowth</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe on the Key of Droghedah, one o<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther houſe in Harpies lane, one garden plot in S. Johns lane, an houſe or tenement in Ri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chards town with ſeve<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ral acres of land, ſeve<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ral houſes and lands in Mollincroſſe, certain houſes and lands in the town and fields of Col<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lem.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dowdal Pa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>trick</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Cook<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, one void piece of ground joyning on the weſt upon the Cor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ner houſe of Bridge<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, and extending on the Eaſt to the ſigne of the Bull on the Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chant-key.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Louth.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Slane.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Regskon and the mill thereof.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Atherdee.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Coologs land. One houſe and backſide at the middle gate of A<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>therdee, one houſe and backſide in the High<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet of Atherdee, one houſe and backſide in the ſaid ſtreet, 60 acres of land in the fields of Atherdee.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Dundalke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballymacklyot.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Dowdall Mat<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thew</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe and garden in Thomas-ſtreet, one houſe and garden in Francis ſtreet, one houſe and garden in Patrick ſtreet: in Kilmainham ten acres of land.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Weſtmeath</p>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Louth</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Delvine.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Cloran, Corcullintragh.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Slan.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>One houſe and back<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſide in Slane.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Deece.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>A mortgage of 200 l. on Lumbardſtown and Fi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dorffe. <hi>Ratooth.</hi> A mortgage of 200 l. upon Smiths town, Himlingſtone and A<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>glaſtan.</p>
                        <p>In Louth 2 acres, in Dundalk two houſes and eight acres.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="63" facs="tcp:136892:34"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Draycott Henry</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in S. Mi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chaels lane.</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>Meath</p>
                        <p>Louth.</p>
                        <p>Weſtmeath</p>
                        <p>Wexford.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Duleeke.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Momantown, Colpe, the little Bebeg, great Be<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>beg, Duleek, Lough, Graycots, Corballid, Routhgrainge, Calangh town, Miltown, Rod<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>der, Fullerſtown, Kilnac<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>daſland, Davistown, both the Graggs, Balgeeth, Scalernagh, Febeg, Colpe, Kells, Drogheda. Febeg, the Rectory of S. Leonard of Dundalk. The Rectory of Killan and Garr.</p>
                        <p>Norriſtown and Clares<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Dipford and Crooked more.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Ellcock Eliza<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>beth</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Pipe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Eiffe John</cell>
                     <cell>The Monaſtery of S. Thomas near Dublin.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fanning Roſe</cell>
                     <cell>Houſes ſeveral, &amp;c.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fullam Ni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cholas</cell>
                     <cell>Houſes ſeveral, &amp;c.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Fleming Roſe <hi>al.</hi> Quine</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in Oxman<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, three tenements and 12 acres of ground in Santhy, 2 tenements near Youngs caſtle, one other houſe in Oxman<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, and one near S. Michaels Church ſtile.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Gernon Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas</cell>
                     <cell>Houſes ſeveral.</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Hore Philip of Kilſalchon</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe in High<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, two in Cook<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, one in S. Brides ſtreet called Henry the eighth, two in New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet, houſes in S. Fran<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cis ſtreet, ſeveral houſes and gardens in S. Maries</cell>
                     <cell>Meath.</cell>
                     <cell>Clatterstown, Bulls town, and ſome land in in Caleſtown, the Man<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nor of Ballemalſhalriſh, <hi>al.</hi> Shalriſh and Kildow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>an, Balliſhelan, Tracris<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town, Harniſtown, the Dirr.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <pb n="64" facs="tcp:136892:35"/>
                  <row>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Abbeys, 1 houſe on Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chants key formerly cal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>led Fitz Simons houſe. The mannor houſe and lands of Killſhalcon, Dunmake, Thorntown, Coolcoye, Carreſtown, the Ruth, Balkhale, Bed<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ford, Sradbally, great Kings town, Rathlucas town, Longhyhill, ſe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>veral houſes and gar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dens in Luske, the town of Caſtleknock, Iriſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>town Hares town, Ri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kenhead, and Caſtle Curragh.</cell>
                     <cell>Wexford</cell>
                     <cell>Graigſhallagh, Pole<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hore, Mortgages of 140 l. on Lawrence Bea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lies land in Stradbally, 140 l. on Paſlaſtown and Mateſtown with ſeveral other Mortgages, three houſes, the Caſtle hills, ſome lands in Tumen.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Jordan John</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>One houſe in Keſars lane, and another on Colledg green.</p>
                        <p>Balmuguire, one meſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſuage and 15 acres in in Luske, Clomedan <hi>al.</hi> Aſhtown, one houſe and 2 acres in Swords, 5 tenements and 26 acres in Cromlin.</p>
                     </cell>
                     <cell>Kings</cell>
                     <cell>Four tenements and gardens in Philipstown.</cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Lambert Phi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lip</cell>
                     <cell>One houſe near New<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gate.</cell>
                     <cell>Wexford</cell>
                     <cell>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Fort.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Ballyheire, Beng, Bally<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>wich, Ballicollan, little Killian, Muckrath, Collkeran, the village o 9 acres and Chappel, Ballycrinegan.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Shilmaleere.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Marſhals town.</p>
                        <p>
                           <hi>Barge.</hi>
                        </p>
                        <p>Richards town.</p>
                        <p>City Wexford.</p>
                        <p>Three houſes.</p>
                     </cell>
                  </row>
                  <row>
                     <cell>Lynch Bar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tholomew</cell>
                     <cell> </cell>
                     <cell>Roſcom<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mon.</cell>
                     <cell>Scaldpark, and the four quarters of Ballinehoe.</cell>
                  </row>
               </table>
            </p>
            <pb facs="tcp:136892:35"/>
         </div>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
